Downloaded from
YTS.MX
&gt;&gt; ON MARCH 27, 2023, THREE NINE
YEAR OLDS EVELYN DIECKHAUS,
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
&gt;&gt; ON MARCH 27, 2023, THREE NINE
YEAR OLDS EVELYN DIECKHAUS,
WILLIAM KINNEY, AND HALLIE
SCRUGGS, ALONG WITH DR.
KATHERINE KOONCE, CYNTHIA PEAK
AND MIKE HILL WALKED INTO
THE COVENANT SCHOOL AND DIDN'T
WALK OUT.
THE COMMUNITY OF SORROW OVER
THIS AND THE 130 MASS SHOOTINGS
IN THE U.S. THIS YEAR ALONE,
STRETCHES FROM COAST TO COAST.
I WANTED TO PERSONALLY STAND UP
HERE AND SHARE THIS MOMENT
BECAUSE ON AUGUST 21, 2008, I
WATCHED RYAN MCDONALD, MY
15-YEAR-OLD CLASSMATE AT
CENTRAL HIGH SCHOOL IN
KNOXVILLE, TENNESSEE LOSE HIS
LIFE TO A GUN IN THE
SCHOOL CAFETERIA.
TONIGHT'S BROADCAST IS DEDICATED
TO THE EVER-GROWING LIST OF
FAMILIES, FRIENDS, SURVIVORS,
WITNESSES, AND RESPONDERS WHOSE
LIVES CONTINUE TO BE FOREVER
CHANGED BY GUN VIOLENCE.
I PRAY THAT THE CLOSENESS AND
COMMUNITY WE FEEL THROUGH THE
NEXT FEW HOURS OF MUSIC CAN SOON
TURN INTO ACTION THAT MOVES US
FORWARD TOGETHER TO CREATE
CHANGE FOR THE SAFETY OF OUR
KIDS AND LOVED ONES.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; WELL, I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING IN
HERE!
BUT IF THIS IS AUSTIN, I STILL
LOVE YA!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪
THAT NEON SUN'S A-RISIN'
I'M SITTIN' HERE, ADMIRIN'
THE SUMMER DRESS THAT'S SHININ'
THROUGH HAD JUST ENOUGH TO TELL
YOU THE TRUTH
DON'T WANNA SCOOT THE BOOTS
WITH NO BODY
GET STRAIGHT TEQUILA DRUNK
ON NO BODY
WRAP THESE ARMS
AROUND NO BODY
NO BODY BUT YOURS
DON'T WANNA SHADOW DANCE
WITH NO BODY
SLIDE SOME COTTON
OFF OF NO BODY
DON'T WANNA WAKE UP
KISSIN' NO BODY
NO BODY BUT YOURS
♪
HONEYSUCKLE TALKIN'
LAST CALL OLD MILWAUKIN'
OUT THERE TO A CHECKERED CAB
B-LINE TO YOUR CONDO
CONWAY ON THE STEREO
GIRL, I'D LOVE TO LAY YOU DOWN,
DOWN, DOWN
DON'T WANNA SCOT THE BOOTS
WITH NO BODY
GET STRAIGHT TEQUILA DRUNK
ON NO BODY
WRAP THESE ARMS
AROUND NO BODY
NO BODY BUT YOURS
DON'T WANNA SHADOW DANCE
WITH NO BODY
SLIDE SOME COTTON
OFF OF NO BODY
DON'T WANNA WAKE UP
KISSIN' NO BODY
NO BODY BUT YOURS
♪
DON'T WANNA HOLD NO BODY
LAY EYES ON NO BODY
LOVE UP ON NO BODY
DON'T WANNA SCOOT THE BOOTS
WITH NO BODY
GET STRAIGHT TEQUILA DRUNK
ON NO BODY
WRAP THESE ARMS
AROUND NO BODY
NO BODY BUT YOURS
DON'T WANNA SHADOW DANCE
WITH NO BODY
SLIDE SOME COTTON OFF
OF NO BODY
♪ DON'T WANNA WAKE UP ♪
♪ KISSIN' NO BODY ♪
♪ NO BODY BUT YOURS ♪
♪ DON'T WANNA WAKE UP ♪
♪ KISSIN' NO BODY ♪
♪ NO BODY BUT YOURS ♪
&gt;&gt; Announcer: LIVE FROM AUSTIN
TEXAS, THIS IS THE 2023 CMT
MUSIC AWARDS ON CBS!
HOSTED BY KELSEA BALLERINI
AND KANE BROWN
WITH PERFORMANCES BY
ALANIS MORISSETTE,
BLAKE SHELTON,
CARLY PEARCE,
CARRIE UNDERWOOD,
CODY JOHNSON,
THE BLACK CROWES
AND DARIUS RUCKER,
GARY CLARK, JR.
GWEN STEFANI,
INGRID ANDRESS,
JELLY ROLL,
KANE BROWN AND KATELYN BROWN,
KEITH URBAN,
KELSEA BALLERINI,
LAINEY WILSON,
MADELINE EDWARDS,
MORGAN WADE,
TYLER HUBBARD,
WYNONNA JUDD
WITH ASHLEY MCBRYDE,
A SPECIAL TRIBUTE TO GARY
ROSSINGTON AND LYNYRD SKYNYRD
WITH BILLY GIBBONS,
PAUL RODGERS, SLASH,
CHUCK LEAVELL,
WARREN HAYNES, WYNONNA JUDD,
AND LEANN RIMES.
FROM THE RAM TRUCK STAGE
AVERY ANNA,
CHAPEL HART,
JACKSON DEAN,
LILY ROSE,
MEGAN MORONEY,
NATE SMITH,
WITH APPEARANCES BY
CHARLES ESTEN,
HARDY,D'AMELIO,-
IAN BOHEN,
JEN LANDON,
JON PARDI,
MADISON BAILEY,
MAX THIERIOT,
MEGAN THEE STALLION,
PARKER MCCOLLUM,
NOAH SCHNAP,
PETER FRAMPTON,
SHANIA TWAIN,
STEVE HOWEY,
TRAVIS KELCE,
AND NOW PLEASE WELCOME
KELSEA BALLERINI AND KANE BROWN!
&gt;&gt; WHAT A WAY TO START THE SHOW!
HOW ARE WE FEELING?
&gt;&gt; BLAKE TOTALLY KILLED IT.
WHAT'S UP, AUSTIN, TEXAS!
&gt;&gt; WE ARE SO EXCITED TO BE HERE
TONIGHT FOR THE FIRST EVER CMT
MUSIC AWARDS IN TEXAS.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE BRINGING THE STARS TO
THE LONE STAR STATE.
&gt;&gt; THAT WAS PUNNY.
I LIKE IT.
THIS IS SO COOL.
LOOKING AROUND THIS ROOM,
IT'S CLEAR.
COUNTRY MUSIC STRETCHES FROM
NASHVILLE, WHERE WE LIVE,
TO AUSTIN TO
YELLOWSTONE
TO THE OUTER BANKS!
&gt;&gt; I WANNA SHOUT OUT THAT WE
HAVE SO MANY INCREDIBLE WOMEN
HERE.
&gt;&gt; YEAH.
&gt;&gt; SHANIA TWAIN
IS IN THE BUILDING!
&gt;&gt; MY QUEEN.
THIS IS, LIKE,
MY DREAM LINEUP.
AMAZING, POWERFUL WOMEN.
LAINEY WILSON.
CARLY PEARCE.
CARRIE UNDERWOOD.
AND Y'ALL,
IT'S NOT JUST THE LINEUP.
THE MUSIC IS ALL ABOUT
EMPOWERMENT AND STRENGTH,
AND WE ALL NEED THAT RIGHT NOW
AND ALWAYS.
&gt;&gt; AND DON'T FORGET ALANIS
MORRISSETTE.
AND GWEN STEFANI'S
IN THE HOUSE!
&gt;&gt; CASUAL.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S RIGHT.
TONIGHT IS COUNTRY'S NIGHT
TO ROCK.
&gt;&gt; THIS PLACE IS PACKED WITH
ROCK STARS, WHICH MAKES PERFECT
SENSE, BECAUSE COUNTRY AND ROCK?
THEY'RE NOT THAT DIFFERENT.
LET US EXPLAIN.
&gt;&gt; WE'VE ALL HEARD OF
"SEX, DRUGS AND ROCK 'N ROLL..."
&gt;&gt; WE HAVE.
IN COUNTRY, IT'S JUST
"HUNTIN, FISHIN, AND LOVING
EVERY DAY."
SAME THING.
&gt;&gt; COUNTRY HAS DARIUS RUCKER.
&gt;&gt; YES, WE SURE DO.
HE'S THE BEST.
AND ROCK HAS...
DARIUS RUCKER.
HONESTLY, THEY SHOULD COLLAB
SOMETIME.
&gt;&gt; WE'RE GONNA SEE DARIUS LATER
WITH THE BLACK CROWES.
&gt;&gt; IT'S INCREDIBLE.
I CAN'T WAIT!
SO GOOD.
&gt;&gt; ROCK HAS POST MALONE.
&gt;&gt; I LOVE POSTY.
I AM ALSO ALWAYS TIRED.
&gt;&gt; HE ROCKS.
&gt;&gt; BUT COUNTRY HAS JELLY ROLL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT'S ON US.
I THINK WE GOT THAT MIXED UP.
&gt;&gt;I THINK WE NAILED IT.
JELLY ROLL HAS SO MANY
NOMINATIONS TONIGHT.
REAL BREAKOUT YEAR FOR HIM,
COME ON NOW.
COME ON.
WE'RE SO HAPPY FOR YOU, BUDDY.
&gt;&gt; Y'ALL, WE'VE GOT SO MANY
GREAT PERFORMANCES.
A BUNCH OF
AWARDS TO HAND OUT.
BUT BEFORE WE GET STARTED, KANE,
THIS IS OUR THIRD TIME
HOSTING TOGETHER.
THIRD TIME'S A CHARM.
&gt;&gt; HAPPY ANNIVERSARY!
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU.
&gt;&gt; I ACTUALLY GOT YOU
SOMETHING.
&gt;&gt; OH, MY GOD.
&gt;&gt; I DID.
&gt;&gt; WOW.
I GOT YOU SOMETHING TOO!
&gt;&gt; YOU DI?
&gt;&gt; YES.
YEEHAW!
WHOO!
&gt;&gt; IT'S A LITTLE SMALL.
I THINK WE LOOK GOOD!
THIS IS THE ONLY COUNTRY AWARDS
SHOW WHERE THE FANS GET TO PICK
THE WINNERS,
AND THERE'S STILL ONE AWARD YOU
CAN HELP DECIDE.
&gt;&gt; IT'S THE BIGGEST AWARD
OF THE NIGHT, VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
WE STARTED OUT WITH 16 NOMINEES
AND NOW WE'RE DOWN TO THE TOP
THREE.
&gt;&gt; TAKE A LOOK.
&gt;&gt; VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
CARRIE UNDERWOOD, HARDY, THANK
GOD.
CAST YOUR VOTES NOW.
FOR CARRIE UNDERWOOD.
FOR HARDY AND LAINEY WILSON.
FOR KANE BROWN AND KATELYN BRO
BROWN, COMMENT...
MAKE SURE TO VOTE NOW.
VIDEO OF THE VOTING IS PRESENTED
BY RAM TRUCKS.
&gt;&gt; YOU CAN CAST YOUR VOTES ON
THE CMT AWARDS FACEBOOK PAGE.
MAKE SURE YOU SHOW YOUR LOVE TO
YOUR FAVORITE ARTIST.
&gt;&gt; WHEN CMT BRINGS IT, WE TAKE
OVER THE WHOLE CITY.
RIGHT NOW, A CMT FAVORITE WHO
DROPPED HIS DEBUT SOLO ALBUM
EARLIER THIS YEAR IS STEPPING
ONTO OUR STAGE IN FRONT OF THE
TEXAS STATE CAPITOL.
&gt;&gt; Y'ALL MAKE SOME NOISE
FOR TYLER HUBBARD!
&gt;&gt; CMT AWARDS!
♪ THEM NEON LIGHTS ♪
♪ LOOK GOOD ON YOU ♪
♪ BUT WE AIN'T GOT ♪
♪ NO ROOM TO MOVE ♪
♪ WE NEED SOME SPACE ♪
♪ AND I KNOW A PLACE ♪
♪ OUTSIDE OF TOWN
WHERE IT DON'T EVER CLOSE DOWN ♪
♪ NO, WE NEVER CLOSE DOWN ♪
♪ YEAH, WE CAN TWO STEP ♪
♪ PUT YOUR BOOTS ON, BABY ♪
♪ WE CAN DO THAT ♪
♪ GIRL, CUT A LITTLE LOOSE ♪
♪ MOVE THAT ♪
♪ AW, YEAH ♪
I'LL TAKE YOU DANCIN'
IN THE COUNTRY
♪ LEVI'S IN THEM LOW BEAMS ♪
♪ SPIN YOU IN SOME RED DIRT ♪
♪ SWEEP YOU OFF OF BOTH FEET ♪
♪ OUT HERE WHERE THE SUN SETS ♪
♪ SILVERADO BACKBEAT ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪ AND NEVER WANNA NOT BE ♪
DANCIN' IN THE COUNTRY ♪
Y'ALL KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT?
♪ YEAH, IT GOES LEFT, RIGHT,
LEFT ♪
♪ YOU MAKIN' ME WANNA SWAY ♪
♪ YOU MAKIN' ME WANNA PLAY ♪
♪ SOME ALABAMA AND JACKSON ♪
♪ GOT YOU 'ROUND MY NECK ♪
♪ MAKIN' ME WANNA STAY ♪
♪ MAKIN' ME WANNA LAY YOU
DOWN HERE IN THE PASTURE ♪
♪ YEAH, WE CAN TWO STEP ♪
♪ PUT YOUR BOOTS ON, BABY ♪
♪ WE CAN DO THAT GIRL ♪
♪ CUT A LITTLE LOOSE ♪
♪ YOU CAN MOVE THAT ♪
♪ MOVE THAT ♪
♪ AW, YEAH ♪
I'LL TAKE YOU DANCIN'
IN THE COUNTRY
♪ LEVI'S IN THEM LOW BEAMS ♪
♪ SPIN YOU IN SOME RED DIRT ♪
♪ SWEEP YOU OFF OF BOTH FEET ♪
♪ OUT HERE WHERE THE SUN SETS ♪
♪ SILVERADO BACKBEAT ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪ AND NEVER WANNA NOT BE ♪
DANCIN' IN THE COUNTRY ♪
♪ WE'RE DANCIN' IN THE COUNTRY ♪
ONE TIME, BOYS!
♪ ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU FEEL THAT HEAT ♪
♪ WATERMELON SUMMER ♪
♪ GET THEM LUCCHESES ♪
♪ STOMPIN' LIKE THE THUNDER ♪
GET YOUR HANDS UP!
ARE WE HAVING A GOOD TIME
TONIGHT OR WHAT?
WHO'S READY TO DANCE TONIGHT?
AUSTIN!
♪ I'LL TAKE YOU DANCIN' ♪
♪ IN THE COUNTRY ♪
♪ LEVI'S IN THEM LOW BEAMS ♪
♪ SPIN YOU IN SOME RED DIRT ♪
♪ SWEEP YOU OFF OF BOTH FEET ♪
♪ OUT HERE WHERE THE SUN SETS ♪
♪ SILVERADO BACKBEAT ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER WANNA GO HOME ♪
♪ AND NEVER WANNA NOT BE ♪
DANCIN' IN THE COUNTRY ♪
WE'RE DANCIN' IN THE COUNTRY ♪
AW, YEAH!
DANCIN' IN THE COUNTRY ♪
WE'RE DANCIN' IN THE COUNTRY ♪
AW, YEAH!
AUSTIN, YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING.
I LOVE YOU.
THANK YOU, CMT.
THANK Y'ALL SO MUCH.
YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING.
SEE YOU LATER, HAVE AN AWESOME
NIGHT.
&gt;&gt; TYLER HUBBARD, EVERYBODY!
ALL RIGHT, WE GOTTA GO BIG IN
TEXAS, AND IT DOESN'T GET MUCH
BIGGER AROUND HERE THAN THIS
GUY.
HE'S FROM AUSTIN
ONE OF THE BEST GUITAR PLAYERS
ON EARTH.
&gt;&gt; HE'S HERE WITH A PERFORMANCE
HONORING THE CITY'S PRIDE AND
JOY, THE LATE, GREAT STEVIE RAY
VAUGHAN.
HERE IS GARY CLARK JR.!
♪ ♪
♪ WELL, THE HOUSE
IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER KNOCKIN' ♪
♪ YEAH, THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER COME ON IN ♪
♪ KICK OFF YOUR SHOES ♪
♪ START LOSIN' THE BLUES ♪
♪ THIS OLD HOUSE ♪
♪ AIN'T GOT NOTHIN' TO LOSE ♪
♪ SEEN IT ALL FOR YEARS ♪
♪ START SPREADIN' THE NEWS ♪
♪ WE GOT ROOM ON THE FLOOR ♪
♪ COME ON, BABY ♪
♪ SHAKE SUMPIN' LOOSE ♪
♪ WELL, THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER KNOCKIN' ♪
♪ YEAH, THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER
♪ COME ON IN ♪
GO AHEAD!
♪ ♪
♪ WELL, THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER KNOCKIN' ♪
♪ YEAH, THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER
♪ COME ON IN ♪
♪ WALKIN' UP THE STREET ♪
♪ YOU CAN HEAR THE SOUND ♪
♪ OF SOME BAD HONKY TONKERS ♪
♪ REALLY LAYIN' IT DOWN ♪
♪ THEY'VE SEEN IT ALL
FOR YEARS ♪
♪ GOT NOTHIN' TO LOSE ♪
♪ SO GET DOWN ON THE FLOOR ♪
♪ SHIMMY 'TIL YOU SHAKE ♪
♪ SUMPIN' LOOSE ♪
♪ WELL, THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER KNOCKIN' ♪
♪ YEAH, THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER
♪ COME ON IN ♪
THE HOUSE IS A ROCKIN' ♪
♪ DON'T BOTHER
♪ COME ON IN ♪
♪ WOO, HOO, HOO, HOO ♪
♪ WOO, OOH, OOM, HOO ♪
♪ WOO, OOH, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; OH, THIS HOUSE IS ROCKIN'!
AUSTEN'S OWN, GARY CLARK JR.,
EVERYBODY.
WE'VE GOT SOME OF THE BIGGEST
NAMES IN MUSIC HERE, BUT THE CMT
MUSIC AWARDS ALSO GIVE A STAGE
TO SOME OF THE MOST EXCITING
BREAKOUT ARTISTS.
AND YOU'RE GONNA GET TO SEE
SIX OF THEM HERE ON THE RAM
TRUCKS STAGE TONIGHT.
KICKING IT OFF, WE'VE GOT AN
ARTIST WHO IS HAVING A HUGE
YEAR.
PERFORMING HER NEW SONG,
"WHATCHA KNOW ABOUT THAT,"
GIVE IT UP FOR MY GIRL,
LILY ROSE!
♪ DO YOU LOVE IT ♪
♪ WHEN IT RAINS ♪
♪ UNDER A TIN ROOF ♪
♪ SITTIN' ON A PORCH SWING ♪
♪ EVER TASTE THAT ♪
♪ SMALL TOWN FAME ♪
♪ YEAH, I THINK WE'RE THE SAME ♪
♪ COME ON, TELL ME, BABY ♪
♪ I WANNA KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT ♪
♪ DO YOU LOVE A LITTLE DOLLY P ♪
♪ COMIN' THROUGH THE DASH ♪
♪ DOES YOUR MAMA'S SWEET TEA ♪
♪ MAKE THE HOT DAYS COLD ♪
♪ MM-MM THAT'S YOU AND ME BOTH ♪
♪ YEAH, WHAT IF I TOLD YOU ♪
♪ I WANT THAT KIND OF LOVE ♪
♪ THAT'S GONNA LAST ♪
♪ YEAH, I WANNA KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; COMING UP, WE HAND OUT THE
FIRST AWARD OF THE NIGHT.
PLUS, PERFORMANCES BY
CARLY PEARCE,
JELLY ROLL, CODY JOHNSON,
KEITH URBAN, AND A SPECIAL
COLLABORATION FROM WYNONA JUDD
AND ASHLEY McBRYDE.
AND AN ALL-STAR CELEBRATION OF
LYNYRD SKYNYRD.
FOR EVEN MORE CMT MUSIC
AWARDS, FOLLOW @CMT!
&gt;&gt; THE 2023 CMT MUSIC AWARDS IS
SPONSORED BY RAM TRUCKS.
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; THE FIRST AWARD IS COMING UP,
AND SINCE THIS OUR FIRST SHOW IN
TEXAS, WE ARE PROUD TO PRESENT
OUR BRAND NEW, CUSTOM MADE,
TEXAS CMT TROPHY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
THAT IS THE REGULAR CMT TROPHY
BUT I ASSURE YOU IT'S AS TEXAS
AS IT GETS.
ARE YOU READY.
CHECK IT OUT.
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S THE CMMT AWARD.
THE EXTRA M STANDS FOR
McCONAUGHEY.
LET'S HAND
ONE OF THESE BABIES OUT.
&gt;&gt; YES.
THANK YOU.
I WILL TAKE ONE OF THOSE.
&gt;&gt; NO, NO, SORRY, MATTHEW.
YOU'VE GOTTA WIN THEM JUST LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE!
TO PRESENT THE FIRST AWARD OF
THE NIGHT, HERE'S ONE OF THE
STARS OF THE MASSIVE HIT SERIES
"STRANGER THINGS," NOAH SCHNAPP!
&gt;&gt; WOW, HELLO.
I'M EXCITED TO BE HERE TO
PRESENT THE AWARD FOR BEST
COLLABORATIVE VIDEO TO A BUNCH
OF ARTISTS THAT I HAVE
ON REPEAT.
COUNTRY SUPERSTARS
JOINING FORCES WITH
POP SINGERS, ROCKERS, AND AN
INCREIBLY TALENTED MARRIED
COUPLE
ALL THESE COLLABORATIONS MERGED
TWO ARTISTIC VOICES TO CREATE
SOMETHING ALTOGETHER NEW
AND BEAUTIFUL.
I LOVE YOU.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES.
&gt;&gt; "WORTH A SHOT."
ELLE KING FEATURING
DIERKS BENTLEY
"WAIT IN THE TRUCK."
HARDY FEATURING LAINEY WILSON.
"WISHFUL DRINKING."
INGRID ANDRESS WITH SAM HUNT.
"THANK GOD."
KANE BROWN &amp; KATELYN BROWN.
"LONGNECK WAY TO GO."
MIDLAND FEATURING JON PARDI.
"SHE LIKES IT."
RUSSELL DICKERSON FEATURING
JAKE SCOTT.
"WHERE WE STARTED."
THOMAS RHETT &amp; KATY PERRY.
COLLABORATIVE VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
&gt;&gt; AND THE WINNER IS...
HARDY FEATURING LAINEY WILSON!
&gt;&gt; ♪ WAIT IN THE TRUCK ♪
♪ JUST WAIT IN THE TRUCK ♪
HAVE MERCY ON ME, LORD ♪
♪ HAVE MERCY ON ME ♪
♪ SHE STILL COMES TO SEE ME FROM
TIME TO TIME ♪
♪ IT WAS WORTH THE PRICE TO SEE
THE BRIGHTER SIDE OF THE GIRL I
PICKED UP THAT NIGHT.
&gt;&gt; IT IS SO HARD NOT TO CUSS.
&gt;&gt; THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
I REMEMBER THE DAY JORDAN
SCHMIDT TO I WROTE THIS SONG
WITH SENT ME THE DEMO.
I SAT DOWN I WAS SO INSPIRED
THAT I WROTE THE ENTIRE SCRIPT,
IF YOU WILL, FOR THE MUSIC VIDEO
BECAUSE OF HOW POWERFUL I KNEW
THE SONG WOULD BE.
I'VE GOT TO SAY THANK YOU TO
LAINEY FOR WORKING SO HARD.
AND JUSTIN, WHO DIRECTED THE
VIDEO.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOURI BEAST.
THINK I
JUST GUY JUST GOT TO SAY I'M SO
PROUD TO BE A SMALL PART OF THE
SONG.
WHEN I HEARD THE SONG, I TELL
YOU, IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY FOR
PEOPLE WHO HAVE BEEN THROUGH
THIS TO FEEL LIKE THEY ARE NOT
ALONE IN ITS OPPORTUNITY FOR THE
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN DOING THIS,
DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED.
THANK YOU SO MUCH TO HARDY.
I LOVE YOU.
&gt;&gt;
MAKE SOME NOISE
FOR JON PARDI!
&gt;&gt; OUR NEXT PERFORMER IS
NOMINATED FOR TWO AWARDS
TONIGHT, INCLUDING FEMALE VIDEO
OF THE YEAR, AND SHE'S HERE WITH
THE SONG THAT WAS NUMBER ONE
IN THE COUNTRY
THIS WEEK.
"WHAT HE DIDN'T DO,"
MAKE SOME NOISE FOR
CARLY PEARCE!
♪ ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S ASKING ♪
♪ WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED ♪
♪ WONDERING WHY IT ♪
♪ ALL WENT WRONG ♪
♪ MAMA ALWAYS SAID ♪
♪ IF YOU CAN'T SAY ♪
♪ SOMETHING NICE ♪
♪ THEN DON'T SAY ANYTHING ♪
♪ AT ALL ♪
♪ I'VE GOT MY SIDE OF THE
STORY ♪
♪ AND HE'S GOT HIS SIDE, TOO ♪
♪ SO, I AIN'T GONNA GO AND ♪
♪ TELL YOU WHAT HE DID ♪
♪ BUT I'LL TELL YOU ♪
♪ WHAT HE DIDN'T DO ♪
♪ TREAT ME RIGHT ♪
♪ PUT ME FIRST ♪
♪ BE A MAN OF HIS WORD ♪
♪ STAY HOME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HE WANTED TO ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIGHT FOR MY LOVE ♪
♪ HOLD ON TIGHT
LIKE IT'S SOMETHING ♪
♪ THAT HE COULDN'T ♪
♪ STAND TO LOSE ♪
♪ THE DEVIL'S IN THE DETAILS ♪
♪ I WON'T TELL ♪
♪ THE HELL THAT ♪
♪ HE PUT ME THROUGH ♪
♪ ALL I KNOW IS IN THE END ♪
♪ IT WASN'T WHAT HE DID, NO ♪
♪ IT WAS WHAT HE DIDN'T DO ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'M ALREADY HALFWAY ♪
♪ OVER HIM AND I AIN'T ♪
♪ TAKING TIME TO TURN AROUND ♪
♪ SO, I'MA TAKE THE HIGH ROAD ♪
♪ EVEN THOUGH WE BOTH KNOW ♪
♪ I COULD RUN HIM ♪
♪ OUT OF THIS TOWN ♪
♪ THAT'S JUST DIRTY LAUNDRY ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED ♪
♪ TO WEAR THE TRUTH ♪
♪ SO, I AIN'T GONNA TELL YOU
EVERYTHING HE DID ♪
♪ BUT I'LL TELL YOU ♪
♪ WHAT HE DIDN'T DO ♪
♪ TREAT ME RIGHT ♪
♪ PUT ME FIRST ♪
♪ BE A MAN OF HIS WORD ♪
♪ STAY HOME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HE WANTED TO ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIGHT FOR MY LOVE ♪
♪ HOLD ON TIGHT ♪
♪ LIKE IT'S SOMETHING ♪
♪ THAT HE COULDN'T ♪
♪ STAND TO LOSE ♪
♪ THE DEVIL'S IN THE DETAILS ♪
♪ I WON'T TELL ♪
♪ THE HELL ♪
♪ THAT HE PUT ME THROUGH ♪
♪ ALL I KNOW IS IN THE END ♪
♪ IT WASN'T WHAT HE DID, NO ♪
♪ IT WAS WHAT HE DIDN'T DO ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I AIN'T MET ♪
♪ THE RIGHT ONE YET ♪
♪ BUT I KNOW WHEN I DO ♪
♪ HE'LL TREAT ME RIGHT ♪
♪ PUT ME FIRST ♪
♪ BE A MAN OF HIS WORD ♪
♪ STAY HOME 'CAUSE HE WANTED
TO ♪
♪ ALWAYS FIGHT FOR MY LOVE ♪
♪ HOLD ON TIGHT ♪
♪ LIKE IT'S SOMETHING ♪
♪ THAT HE CAN'T STAND TO LOSE ♪
♪ THE DEVIL'S IN THE DETAILS ♪
♪ I WON'T TELL ♪
♪ THE HELL ♪
♪ THAT HE PUT ME THROUGH ♪
♪ ALL I KNOW IS IN THE END ♪
♪ IT WASN'T WHAT HE DID, NO ♪
♪ IT WAS WHAT HE DIDN'T DO ♪
♪ ALL I KNOW IS IN THE END ♪
♪ IT WASN'T WHAT HE DID, NO ♪
♪ IT WAS WHAT HE DIDN'T DO ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S UP, CMT FANS!
I'M CODY ALAN.
CHECK THIS PLACE OUT.
I'M HERE IN THE SOLITAIRE GRAND
HARVEST GAME LOUNGE AND IT'S
TAKING PLACE BACKSTAGE
TO EXPERIENCE
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
IT'S SET UP SO THAT ALL THE
STARS HERE TONIGHT GET TO DO
WHAT THEY DO BEST.
THAT IS PLAY.
BECAUSE EVERYONE NEEDS TO CUT
LOOSE, KICK BACK AND HAVE SOME
FUN.
AND FANS AT HOME CAN GET IN ON
THE ACTION TONIGHT.
SCAN THE QR CODE BELOW TO SEE
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO HAVE YOUR OWN
WINNING MOMENT.
HEY!
DUSTIN LYNCH!
IS IT MY TURN YET?
&gt;&gt; WE'LL BE BACK A LITTLE LATER.
&gt;&gt; STILL O COME,
MALE AND FEMALE BREAKTHROUGH
VIDEO OF THE YEAR, PERFORMANCES
FROM LAINEY WILSON
AND CARRIE UNDERWOOD, AND A
SPECIAL COLLABORATION FROM
WYNONNA JUDD AND
ASHLEY McBRYDE.
BE SURE TO CAST YOUR VOTE ON
THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS FACEBOOK
PAGE, VOTING PRESENTED BY
RAM TRUCKS.
THE CMT MUSIC
AWARDS CONTINUES
LIVE FROM AUSTIN, TEXAS.
THIS IS CBS.
&gt;&gt; THE 2023 CMT MUSIC AWARDS
SPONSORED BY
SOLITAIRE GRAND HARVEST.
REINVENTING NOSTALGIC FUN!
DOWNLOAD FOR FREE NOW.
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; KELSEA AND I LOVE NASHVILLE.
BUT GETTING TO HANG OUT IN
AUSTIN THIS WEEK HAS BEEN PRETTY
COOL.
WE LOVE HOT CHICKEN IN
NASHVILLE, BUT YOU GUYS ARE
CRAZY ABOUT BARBECUE.
LIKE, I SMELL BRISKET
EVERYWHERE.
KANE, WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
&gt;&gt; MY POCKET.
&gt;&gt; YOU WANT SOME?
&gt;&gt; THAT'S A PASS
ON POCKET BRISKET, THANKS.
&gt;&gt; RIGHT NOW WE'VE GOT ANOTHER
GENUINE TEXAN HERE TO PRESENT
THE NEXT AWARD.
HE WON BREAKTHROUGH VIDEO OF THE
YEAR IN 2022.
&gt;&gt; HERE IS PARKER McCOLLUM!
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S UP, AUSTIN?
WINNING THIS CATEGORY
LAST YEAR WAS A HIGHLIGHT
SHARE THAT FEELING
WITH TONIGHT'S WINNERS.
SO HOW 'BOUT WE GET RIGHT TO IT.
FIRST UP,
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BREAKTHROUGH FEMALE VIDEO
OF THE YEAR.
"NARCISSIST"
AVERY ANNA.
"IF HE WANTED TO HE COULD"
KYLIE MORGAN,
"PICKUP"
MACKENZIE PORTER,
"TENNESSEE ORANGE"
MEGAN MORONEY,
MORGAN WADE,
"WILDER DAYS"
"FOUND IT IN YOU"
TIERA KENNEDY.
&gt;&gt; AND THE WINNER IS...
MEGAN MORONEY,
"TENNESSEE ORANGE."
&gt;&gt; ♪ I MET SOMEBODY ♪
♪ HE'S GOT BLUE EYES ♪
♪ HE OPENS THE DOOR ♪
♪ HE'S GOT THE DOING THINGS I'VE
NEVER DONE ♪
♪ IN GEORGIA, THEY CALL IT A
SIN ♪
&gt;&gt; WHAT?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
THANK YOU, CMT, SO MUCH.
THANK YOU TO MY FANS.
I WOULDN'T BE APPEAR IF IT
WASN'T FOR Y'ALL.
THANK YOU TO THE INCREDIBLE
VIDEO TEAM AT COLUMBIA FOR
PUTTING THIS TOGETHER THE DAY
THANK YOU TO THE DIRECTOR, JASON
LESTER, FOR REALLY BRINGING MY
IDEAS TO LIFE IN THIS VIDEO.
I ALSO WANT TO THANK MY PARENTS,
ESPECIALLY MY MOM.
BECAUSE MY FLIGHT GOT CANCELED
THE NIGHT BEFORE ENCHANTED DRIVE
ME THROUGH THE NIGHT TO
NASHVILLE.
SO THANK YOU, MOM.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU, CMT.
A HOLY CRAP
&gt;&gt; AND NOW, HERE ARE THE
NOMINEES FOR BREAKTHROUGH MALE
VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
&gt;&gt; "FALL IN LOVE"
BAILEY ZIMMERMAN,
"WILD AS HER"
COREY KENT,
"SOUNDS LIKE
SOMETHING I'D DO"
DRAKE MILLIGAN,
"DON'T COME LOOKIN'"
JACKSON DEAN,
"SON OF A SINNER"
JELLY ROLL,
"WHISKEY ON YOU"
NATE SMITH,
&gt;&gt; AND THE WINNER IS...
JELLY ROLL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; THEY LET A LOSER WIN TONIGHT,
BABY!
THEY LET A LOSER WIN TO MY
CREDIT WANT TO THANK MY RECORD
LABEL, MY MANAGEMENT, MY
BEAUTIFUL WIFE.
THIS IS MORE THAN AN AWARD.
IT'S FOR THE FANS.
THE ONLY FANS VOTING AWARD SHOW
IN AMERICA.
THIS IS FOR TH UNDERDOGS, BABY!
THIS IS FOR THE LOSERS AND THE
HAVE-NOTS.
GOD TAKES THE IMPOSSIBLE AND
MAKES IT LOOK SMALL.
LET'S GO, BABY!
&gt;&gt; CMT HAS ALWAYS BROUGHT FANS
THEIR FAVORITE MUSIC WITH THE
FLAGSHIP SHOW "CMT CROSSROADS"
AND NOW, WITH ALL NEW EPISODES
OF THE LEGENDARY SERIES
"STORYTELLERS."
SINCE A PARAMOUNT+
SUBSCRIPTION IS NOW INCLUDED
WITH A WALMART PLUS MEMBERSHIP,
AT NO ADDITIONAL COST, MEMBERS
CAN STREAM THOSE SHOWS AND GREAT
MUSIC DOCUMENTARIES LIKE
"KACEY MUSGRAVES: STAR CROSSED"
"THE MARFA TAPES,"
AND THE UPCOMING
"WYNONNA JUDD:
BETWEEN HELL AND HALLELUJAH."
PLUS, HIT ORIGINAL SERIES LIKE
THE "YELLOWSTONE" ORIGIN STORIES
"1883" AND "1923,"
"TULSA KING,"
"RABBIT HOLE,"
"JOE PICKETT," AND COMING SOON,
"GREASE:
RISE OF THE PINK LADIES."
ALL THIS AND MORE,
STREAMING ON PARAMOUNT+.
I WAS SO HONORED TO JOIN THE
JUDDS FINAL TOUR AND WITNESS OUR
ARTIST COMMUNITY COME TOGETHER
IN SUPPORT OF MISS WYNONNA JUDD.
THAT JOURNEY IS CAPTURED IN THE
SPECIAL "CMT PRESENTS THE JUDDS:
LOVE IS ALIVE:
THE FINAL CONCERT" THAT WILL
PREMIERE ON APRIL 29TH ON CMT.
OH, MY GOSH, YOU GUYS!
SHE IS HERE NOW.
WITH ANOTHER GREAT ARTIST WHO
JOINED HER THAT HISTORIC NIGHT,
PERFORMING ONE OF WYNONNA'S
FAVORITE SONGS FROM THE '80s.
FOREIGNER'S CLASSIC
"I WANT TO KNOW WHAT LOVE IS."
YOU ARE IN FOR SUCH A TREAT.
PLEASE WELCOME WYNONNA JUDD
AND ASHLEY McBRYDE!
♪ I'VE GOTTA TAKE ♪
♪ A LITTLE TIME ♪
♪ TO THINK THINGS OVER ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I BETTER ♪
♪ READ BETWEEN THE LINES ♪
♪ IN CASE I NEED IT ♪
♪ WHEN I'M OLDER ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ THIS MOUNTAIN ♪
♪ I MUST CLIMB ♪
♪ IT FEELS LIKE THE WORLD'S ♪
♪ UPON MY SHOULDERS ♪
♪ BUT THROUGH THOSE CLOUDS ♪
♪ I SEE LOVE SHINE ♪
♪ IT KEEPS ME WARM ♪
♪ AS LIFE GROWS COLDER ♪
♪ IN MY LIFE ♪
♪ OH, THERE'S BEEN HEARTACHE ♪
♪ AND PAIN ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ IF I CAN FACE IT AGAIN ♪
♪ AND I CAN'T STOP NOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'VE TRAVELED SO FAR ♪
♪ TO CHANGE THIS LONELY LIFE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT LOVE IS ♪
♪ OH, I WANT YOU TO SHOW ME ♪
♪ I WANT TO FEEL WHAT LOVE IS ♪
♪ OH, YES, I KNOW
I WANT YOU TO SHOW ME ♪
♪ YEAH! ♪
♪ GONNA TAKE A LITTLE TIME ♪
♪ A LITTLE TIME ♪
♪ TO LOOK AROUND ME ♪
♪ I'VE GOT NOWHERE ♪
♪ LEFT TO HIDE ♪
♪ LOOKS LIKE LOVE ♪
♪ HAS FINALLY FOUND ME ♪
♪ IN MY LIFE ♪
♪ THERE'S BEEN HEARTACHE ♪
♪ AND PAIN ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ IF I CAN FACE IT AGAIN ♪
♪ AND I CAN'T STOP NOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'VE TRAVELED TOO FAR ♪
♪ TO CHANGE THIS LONELY LIFE ♪
♪ I WANT TO KNOW WHAT LOVE IS ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO SHOW ME ♪
♪ I WANT TO FEEL WHAT LOVE IS ♪
TALKIN' ABOUT LOVE THAT YOU
FEEL INSIDE ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU CAN SHOW ME ♪
MAMA, YOU NEED TO HERE TONIGHT
I MISS YOU AND I LOVE YOU
♪ I WANT TO KNOW WHAT LOVE IS ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU CAN SHOW ME ♪
♪ YEAH! ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; GET READY TO ROCK ON THE
STREETS OF AUSTIN WITH
KEITH URBAN AND MORE
PERFORMANCES, INCLUDING
ALANIS MORRISETTE,
THE BLACK CROWES AND DARIUS
RUCKER.
PLUS, SHANIA TWAIN RECEIVES
THE CMT EQUAL PLAY AWARD.
WE'RE LIVE BEHIND THE SCENES
OF THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS!
CHECK IT OUT ON YOUTUBE NOW.
THIS IS CBS.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE WELCOME THREE-TIME
GRAMMY WINNER
MEGAN THEE STALLION.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; OKAY!
[CHEERING]
OKAY, Y'ALL LET ME SAY IT.
Y'ALL MAKING ME FEEL TOO GOOD.
CMT HAS BEEN A LEADER IN THE
FIGHT FOR DIVERSITY AND
INCLUSION IN COUNTRY MUSIC FOR
THE PAST DECADE, WITH
INITIATIVES LIKE NEXT WOMEN OF
COUNTRY AND CMT EQUAL PLAY
AND EQUAL ACCESS.
THE CMT EQUAL PLAY AWARD
RECOGNIZES TRAILBLAZERS WHO USE
THEIR PLATFORM TO BREAK
BARRIERS, SPEAK OUT AGAINST
INJUSTICES, AND CHALLENGE
THE STATUS QUO.
[CHEERING]
THIS YEAR, WE ARE RECOGNIZING
THE INCREDIBLE SHANIA TWAIN!
UH-HUH!
SHANIA TWAIN!
OKAY!
SHANIA ISN'T JUST THE
BIGGEST-SELLING COUNTRY FEMALE
ARTIST OF ALL TIME,
SHE HAS SHATTERED CEILINGS
AND REDEFINED STYLE AND SOUND
IN COUNTRY MUSIC AND BEYOND.
SHE HAS BEEN OUTSPOKEN.
I DON'T WANT TO CHEESE THIS
AGAINST HATE OF EVERY KIND,
I JUST MET HER.
SHE IS MY NEW BESTIE.
SHE HAS BEEN AN OUTSPOKEN
ALLY AGAINST HATE OF EVERY KIND,
CALLING OUT GENDER GAPS, AGEISM,
YES.
UH-HUH, YES!
YES, SHANIA!
IMPACTING INEQUALITIES
AGAINST THE LGBTQ+ COMMUNITY,
AND MORE.
SHE'S AN INSPIRATION TO ME
AND MILLIONS OF OTHERS!
PLEASE WELCOME THIS YEAR'S
EQUAL PLAY AWARD RECIPIENT,
SHANIA TWAIN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU, MEGAN.
YOU'RE SO TALL.
I LOST MY HAT.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LET ME START BY SAYING LET'S GO,
GIRLS.
LISTEN, WHEN I WROTE THE PHRASE
"MAN, I FEEL LIKE A WOMAN," I
HAD NO IDEA IT WOULD BECOME AN
UNDERCURRENT OF A DECADES LONG
CAREER.
IT'S AMAZING HOW JUST ONE
STATEMET CAN EMPOWER SO MANY.
"MAN!
I FEEL LIKE A WOMAN" HAS BEEN
ADOPTED BY AN ARRAY OF FANTASTIC
COMMUNITIES ALL AROUND THE WORLD
AND BECOME A GENUINE PATH OF
POWER AND PROGRESS FOR WOMEN.
WOMEN IN COUNTRY MUSIC.
WHICH BRINGS ME SO MUCH JOY.
THANK YOU TO CMT FOR PUSHING THE
EQUAL PLAY AGENDA AND THANK YOU
FOR ALWAYS SUPPORTING ME.
IN FACT, YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU MAY
NOT KNOW THIS.
BUT THE CMT RISING STAR AWARD
WAS MY VERY FIRST AWARD EVER.
30 YEARS AGO.
THAT WAS IN 1993.
CMT HOLDS A VERY SPECIAL PLACE
IN MY HEART.
AND I PROMISE I WILL CONTINUE TO
CHAMPION THE MANY OUTSTANDING
COUNTRY ARTISTS WHO ARE NOT
CURRENTLY PLAYED.
THEY ARE NOT STREAMED, TOURS
SIGNED OR AWARDED AT THE LEVEL
THEY DESERVE SO I BELIEVE IN AN
ALL-INCLUSIVE COUNTRY MUSIC.
WE ARE A FAMILY.
THIS IS A GENRE OF MUSIC WITH A
RICH HISTORY THAT RAISED AND
NURTURED MY OWN SONGWRITING AND
PERFORMANCE AND RECORDING CAREER
FROM CHILDHOOD.
CURRENTLY THE INDUSTRY STANDARD
DOES A REAL DISSERVICE TO THIS.
LET US, THE COUNTRY MUSIC
INDUSTRY, DO OUR PART TO CLOSE
WORK SPACE FOR ALL TALENT.
THIS YEAR, I'M TAKING MANY
AMAZING ARTISTS ON MY QUEEN OF
KNEE
TOUR ROBIN, PRISCILLA, SEVERAL
MORE.
MY HOPE IS THAT THIS OPPORTUNITY
AND SPOTLIGHT IMPRESSES YOU MU
MUCH.
AND LIFTS UP THE CAREERS OF
THESE VERY TALENTED PEOPLE ON
THEIR JOURNEY.
I WILL CONTINUE TO DO MY BEST AS
A TRAILBLAZER AND TOGETHER,
LET'S ENSURE THAT ALL OUR FELLOW
ARTISTS GET EQUAL PLAY
REGARDLESS OF GENDER, AGE, OR
RACE.
THANK YOU AGAIN FOR HONORING ME.
SPECIAL THANK YOU TO ALL MY
FANS.
I AM TRULY TOUCHED BY THIS
MOMENT.
THANK YOU.
PLEASE WELCOME
THE STAR OF
THE NEW CBS SERIES "TRUE LIES,"
BONAFIDE TEXAN STEVE HOWEY!
&gt;&gt; THE STARS AT NIGHT
ARE BIG AND BRIGHT
&gt;&gt; DEEP IN THE HEART OF TEXAS!
&gt;&gt; YES, THANK YOU!
WE'RE IN LONGHORN COUNTRY, BABY.
ALL RIGHT.
I JUST HAD TO BE HERE FOR THE
FIRST EVER CMT MUSIC AWARDS
THERE'S CODY.
HE JUST POINTED AT ME.
FIRST EVER CMT MUSIC AWARDS
IN MY HOME STATE.
I WAS BORN IN SAN ANTONIO.
I LOVE AUSTIN.
THIS NEXT ARTIST ISN'T JUST
BIG.
HE'S TEXAS BIG.
HE TOOK OVER COUNTRY WITH HIS
BREAKOUT HIT LAST YEAR, TOOK
HOME A FEW CMTS, AND HAS
JUST KEPT GOING EVER SINCE.
WITH HIS LATEST HIT,
"HUMAN," HERE IS CODY JOHNSON!
♪ ♪
♪ I THOUGHT BY NOW ♪
♪ I'D HAVE IT FIGURED OUT ♪
♪ HOW NOT TO MAKE ♪
♪ THE EASY THING ♪
♪ SO HARD TO DO ♪
♪ I BET THAT I'D BE ♪
♪ FURTHER DOWN THIS ROAD ♪
♪ IF I COULD READ THE SIGNS ♪
♪ THAT POINT ME TO THE TRUTH ♪
♪ I NEVER PLANNED ON ♪
♪ BEING NOTHIN' BUT A COWBOY ♪
♪ BUT SOMEWHERE ♪
♪ I PICKED UP THIS OLD GUITAR ♪
♪ GIRL, ALL I CAN SAY ♪
♪ IS THAT I'M SORRY ♪
♪ IF I GET KIND OF CARELESS ♪
♪ WITH YOUR HEART ♪
ALL THE MIDNIGHTS
♪ CHASING ALL THAT EMPTY ♪
♪ STILL AIN'T GOT IT RIGHT ♪
♪ ALL THE CRAZY ♪
♪ ALL THE GYPSY ♪
♪ I GUESS ALL I'M SAYIN' IS
FORGIVE ME ♪
♪ IF I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M
DOING ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M STILL LEARNIN' TO
BE HUMAN ♪
♪ SO FAR I'VE BEEN GOOD ♪
♪ AT BURNIN' BRIDGES ♪
♪ STRIKE A MATCH ♪
♪ AND RIDE RIGHT OUT OF TOWN ♪
♪ BLESS YOUR HEART FOR NEVER
TRYIN' TO FIX ME ♪
♪ OR QUIT ME ♪
♪ OR SLOW ME DOWN ♪
♪ ALL THE MIDNIGHTS ♪
♪ CHASING ALL THAT EMPTY ♪
♪ STILL AIN'T GOT IT RIGHT ♪
♪ ALL THE CRAZY ♪
♪ ALL THE GYPSY ♪
♪ I GUESS ALL I'M SAYIN' IS
FORGIVE ME ♪
♪ IF I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT I'M DOING ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M STILL LEARNIN' ♪
♪ TO BE HUMAN ♪
AIN'T WE ALL, HUH, AUSTIN?
♪ ALL THE HIGHWAYS ♪
♪ PLAYIN' OUTLAW ♪
♪ ROLLIN' OUTTA NOWHERE ♪
♪ WITH THE BRAKES OFF ♪
♪ ALL THE CRAZY ♪
♪ AND THE WHISKEY ♪
♪ WAKIN' UP AND WONDERIN' ♪
♪ WHAT HIT ME ♪
♪ WHOA, FORGIVE ME ♪
♪ I REALLY DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT I'M DOIN' ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M STILL ♪
♪ LEARNIN' TO BE HUMAN ♪
♪ MMM, STILL LEARNIN' ♪
♪ TO BE HUMAN ♪
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; CODY JOHNSON!
THIS NEXT ARTIST IS KNOWN
FOR HIS MASSIVE SONGS, HIS
INCREDIBLE GUITAR CHOPS AND FOR
HIS GAME CHANGING PERFORMANCES
RIGHT HERE AT THE CMT MUSIC
AWARDS.
TONIGHT, HE'S COMING
FROM OUR CAPITOL STAGE
IN THE HEART OF AUSTIN,
KEITH URBAN, EVERYBODY!
♪ ♪
♪ YOU MADE UP YOUR MIND ♪
♪ GOT OFF THE COUCH ♪
♪ YOU DID UP YOUR HAIR ♪
♪ NOW YOU'RE GOIN' OUT ♪
♪ YOU PUT ON THAT PARTY DRESS ♪
♪ EVEN THOUGH ♪
♪ YOUR HEART'S A MESS ♪
♪ YOUR FRIENDS SWUNG BY ♪
♪ YOU JUMPED IN THE CAR ♪
♪ YOU WALKED IN HERE ♪
♪ AND NOW HERE WE ARE ♪
♪ PUTTIN' THE HURTIN' ♪
♪ ON SOME JOSE ♪
♪ AND CATCHIN' UP ♪
♪ WHILE THE BAND PLAYS ♪
♪ YOU SAY YOU MISS THE GIRL ♪
♪ YOU USED TO BE ♪
♪ BET I CAN FIND HER ♪
♪ IF YOU LET ME ♪
♪ I CAN PUT THE SMILE ♪
♪ RIGHT BACK WHERE ♪
♪ YOUR SMILE GOES ♪
♪ DREAMS BACK IN ♪
♪ WHAT YOU SEE ♪
♪ WHEN YOUR EYES CLOSE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE BUZZ ♪
♪ THAT YOU FEEL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SIP SLOW ♪
♪ SLOW DANCE ♪
♪ RIGHT BACK ♪
♪ IN YOUR DIRT ROAD ♪
♪ I CAN PUT THE SUN ♪
♪ RIGHT BACK IN YOUR SUNSHINE ♪
♪ BRING A LITTLE LOVE ♪
♪ BACK INTO YOUR LATE NIGHT ♪
♪ AIN'T GOTTA BE NOTHIN' MORE ♪
♪ THAN ONE MORE DRINK ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I CAN TAKE THE
BLUE ♪
♪ OUT OF YOUR BROWN EYES, BABY ♪
♪ ♪
♪ AND THAT WILD SIDE ♪
♪ THAT YOU LEARNED TO TAME ♪
♪ SHE'LL ROLL IN ♪
♪ LIKE A MIDNIGHT TRAIN ♪
♪ ALMOST LIKE SHE NEVER ♪
♪ LEFT HERE ♪
♪ AND I'LL BE READY ♪
♪ BABY, WHEN SHE GETS HERE ♪
♪ I CAN PUT THE SMILE ♪
♪ RIGHT BACK WHERE ♪
♪ YOUR SMILE GOES ♪
♪ DREAMS BACK IN ♪
♪ WHAT YOU SEE ♪
♪ WHEN YOUR EYES CLOSE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE BUZZ ♪
♪ THAT YOU FEEL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SIP SLOW ♪
♪ SLOW DANCE RIGHT BACK ♪
♪ IN YOUR DIRT ROAD ♪
♪ I CAN PUT THE SUN ♪
♪ RIGHT BACK IN YOUR SUNSHINE ♪
♪ BRING A LITTLE LOVE ♪
♪ BACK INTO YOUR LATE NIGHT ♪
♪ AIN'T GOTTA BE ♪
♪ NOTHIN' MORE THAN ♪
♪ ONE MORE DRINK ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I CAN TAKE THE
BLUE ♪
♪ OUT OF YOUR BROWN EYES, BABY ♪
♪ ♪
♪ PUT THE FULL ♪
♪ BACK IN YOUR HALF EMPTY ♪
♪ AND PUT THE TWO ♪
♪ IN YOUR STEP AGAIN ♪
♪ ABOUT TO SEE ♪
♪ WHERE LEANIN' IN GETS ME ♪
♪ BABY, JUST SAY WHEN ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I CAN PUT THE SMILE ♪
♪ RIGHT BACK ♪
♪ WHERE YOUR SMILE GOES ♪
♪ DREAMS BACK IN ♪
♪ WHAT YOU SEE ♪
♪ WHEN YOUR EYES CLOSE ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE BUZZ ♪
♪ THAT YOU FEEL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SIP SLOW ♪
♪ SLOW DANCE RIGHT BACK ♪
♪ IN YOUR DIRT ROAD ♪
♪ I CAN PUT THE SUN ♪
♪ RIGHT BACK IN YOUR SUNSHINE ♪
♪ BRING A LITTLE LOVE ♪
♪ BACK INTO YOUR LATE NIGHT ♪
♪ AIN'T GOTTA BE NOTHIN' MORE ♪
♪ THAN ONE MORE DRINK ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I CAN TAKE THE
BLUE ♪
♪ OUT OF YOUR BROWN EYES, BABY ♪
♪ MMM, TAKE THE BLUE OUT OF ♪
♪ YOUR BROWN EYES, BABY ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; I LOVE YOU, AUSTIN!
THANK YOU, CMT!
&gt;&gt; HOW MUCH DO WE LOVE KEITH
URBAN?
SO GREAT TO SEE ALL THOSE FANS
OUT THERE.
EARLIER TONIGHT WE ANNOUNCED
THAT THE WINNER THE GROUP DO A
VIDEO IS ZAC BROWN BAND FOR OUT
IN THE MIDDLE.
SPEAKING OF THE MIDDLE , WE ARE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE SHOW NOW.
KANE HAD A SNACK.
HE HAD A BRISKET.
IT'S MY TURN.
TIME TO INTRODUCE MY BURRITO
CLUTCH.
DO YOU MIND?
IT'S DIFFERENT DOWN HERE.
SPEAKING OF THINGS THAT ARE
CLUTCH,
HERE TO PERFORM "WHISKEY ON
YOU," FROM THE RAM TRUCKS STAGE,
IT'S NATE SMITH!
♪ LINE 'EM UP ♪
♪ POUR 'EM TALL ♪
♪ HERE'S TO US ♪
♪ HAPPILY NEVER AFTER ALL ♪
♪ AIN'T GONNA WASTE ♪
♪ ONE MORE NIGHT ♪
♪ MISSING, WANTING YOU BACK ♪
♪ NO, I AIN'T GONNA CRY ♪
♪ ANOTHER TEAR IN THIS GLASS ♪
♪ YOU DIDN'T WASTE ANY TIME ♪
♪ FINDING SOMEBODY NEW ♪
♪ SO I AIN'T GONNA WASTE ♪
♪ ANOTHER DROP OF WHISKEY ♪
♪ ON YOU ♪
♪ NO, I AIN'T GONNA WASTE ♪
♪ ANOTHER DROP OF WHISKEY ♪
♪ ON YOU ♪
♪ NO, I AIN'T ♪
♪ NO, I AIN'T GONNA WASTE ♪
♪ ANOTHER DROP OF WHISKEY ♪
♪ ON YOU ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; NEXT, LAINEY WILSON WITH HER
HIT "HEART LIKE A TRUCK,"
AND GWEN STEFANI TAKES THE STAGE
WITH HER ICONIC "JUST A GIRL,"
WITH SPECIAL GUEST
CARLY PEARCE.
WHO WILL WIN VIDEO OF THE YEAR?
IT'S UP TO YOU.
CAST YOUR VOTES RIGHT NOW
ON THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS FACEBOOK
PAGE.
THE VOTING IS PRESENTED BY
RAM TRUCKS.
THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS CONTINUES
LIVE FROM AUSTIN, TEXAS.
THIS IS CBS.
&gt;&gt; THE 2023 CMT MUSIC AWARDS
SPONSORED BY...
PROGRESSIVE.
SAVE WHEN YOU BUNDLE
AUTO, HOME, OR MOTORCYCLE
INSURANCE.
&gt;&gt; WELCOME BACK TO THE 2023
CMT MUSIC AWARDS.
I'M BACK HERE IN THE SOLITAIRE
GRAND HARVEST GAME LOUNGE.
DUSTIN LYNCH IS HAVING A BLAST
WITH ALL THE GAMES
IN THIS PLACE.
THE NEXT THREE PRESENTERS HAVE
A LOT IN COMMON.
THEY'VE ALL WORKED WITH
LAINEY WILSON, AND NONE OF THEM
CAN TELL ME ANYTHING ABOUT
THE NEXT SEASON
OF "YELLOWSTONE."
ALTHOUGH HARDY HAS SOME GOOD
THEORIES.
PLEASE WELCOME IAN BOHEN,
JEN LANDON, AND HARDY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; THIS NEXT PERFORMER IS ONE OF
MY FAVORITE ARTISTS IN COUNTRY
MUSIC, AND I'M NOT ONLY SAYING
THAT BECAUSE SHE PLAYS
MY GIRLFRIEND ON "YELLOWSTONE."
&gt;&gt; SHE CAN ACT, SHE'S A GREAT
SONGWRITER, SHE'S GOT
A KILLER VOICE.
AND SHE'S ONE OF THE NICEST
PEOPLE YOU'LL NEVER MEET.
&gt;&gt; PERFORMING
"HEART LIKE A TRUCK,"
NUMBER ONE SONG IN COUNTRY
THIS WEEK.
HERE IS OUR FRIEND AND MY
SOON-TO-BE TOURING MATE,
LAINEY WILSON!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
♪ I NEVER STAY ♪
♪ IN ONE PLACE TOO LONG ♪
♪ THE DIRT ROAD SINGIN' ME ♪
♪ A SIREN'S SONG I GOTTA ♪
♪ FIND A FIELD ♪
♪ I NEED TO SPIN MY WHEELS ♪
♪ I GOTTA A'HANKERIN' ♪
♪ FOR FOUR WIDE TIRES ♪
♪ AND I CAN'T HELP IT ♪
♪ IT'S THE WAY I'M WIRED ♪
♪ 'FORE YOU GET TOO CLOSE ♪
♪ BOY, YOU NEED TO KNOW ♪
♪ I GOT A HEART LIKE A TRUCK ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN DRUG THROUGH ♪
♪ THE MUD ♪
♪ RUNS ON DREAMS AND GASOLINE ♪
♪ AND THAT OLE HIGHWAY ♪
♪ HOLDS THE KEY ♪
♪ IT'S GOT A LEAD FOOT ♪
♪ DOWN WHEN IT'S LEAVIN' ♪
♪ LORD KNOWS IT'S TAKEN ♪
♪ A HELL OF A BEATIN' ♪
♪ A LITTLE BIT OF LOVE ♪
♪ IS ALL THAT IT'S NEEDIN' ♪
♪ BUT IT'S GOOD AS IT IS TOUGH ♪
♪ I GOT A HEART LIKE A TRUCK ♪
♪ THERE AIN'T NO BRAKIN' ♪
♪ WHEN I THROW IT IN DRIVE ♪
♪ DON'T ALWAYS KEEP IT
IN BETWEEN THE LINES ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE READY
♪ PEDAL DOWN STATE OF MIND ♪
♪ BOY, I TELL YOU WHAT ♪
♪ YOU BETTER BUCKLE UP ♪
♪ I GOT A HEART LIKE A TRUCK ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN DRUG THROUGH ♪
♪ THE MUD ♪
♪ RUNS ON DREAMS AND GASOLINE ♪
♪ AND THAT OLD HIGHWAY ♪
♪ HOLDS THE KEY ♪
♪ IT'S GOT A LEAD FOOT DOWN ♪
♪ WHEN IT'S LEAVIN' ♪
♪ LORD KNOWS IT'S TAKEN ♪
♪ A HELL OF A BEATIN' ♪
♪ A LITTLE BIT OF LOVE ♪
♪ IS ALL THAT IT'S NEEDIN' ♪
♪ BUT IT'S GOOD AS IT IS TOUGH ♪
♪ I GOT A HEART LIKE A TRUCK ♪
♪ ♪
♪ GO ON AND SEE ♪
♪ IF YOU CAN ♪
♪ KNOCK OFF THE DUST, YEAH ♪
♪ SHINE IT UP, REV IT UP ♪
♪ AND LET IT RUN, YEAH ♪
♪ IT GETS A HIGH RIDIN' ♪
♪ OFF INTO THE SUN, YEAH ♪
♪ I GOT A HEART LIKE A TRUCK ♪
♪ IT'S BEEN ♪
♪ DRUG THROUGH THE MUD ♪
♪ RUNS ON DREAMS AND GASOLINE ♪
♪ AND THAT OLD HIGHWAY ♪
♪ HOLDS THE KEY ♪
♪ IT'S GOT A LEAD FOOT DOWN ♪
♪ WHEN IT'S LEAVIN' ♪
♪ LORD KNOWS IT'S TAKEN ♪
♪ A HELL OF A BEATIN' ♪
♪ A LITTLE BIT OF LOVE ♪
♪ IS ALL THAT IT'S NEEDIN' ♪
♪ BUT IT'S GOOD AS IT IS TOUGH ♪
♪ I GOT A HEART ♪
♪ LIKE A TRUCK ♪
♪ GO ON AND SEE ♪
♪ IF YOU CAN ♪
♪ KNOCK OFF THE DUST, YEAH ♪
♪ SHINE IT UP, REV IT UP ♪
♪ AND LET IT RUN, YEAH ♪
♪ IT GETS A HIGH RIDIN' OFF ♪
♪ INTO THE SUN, YEAH ♪
♪ INTO THE SUN ♪
♪ IT GETS A HIGH RIDIN' OFF ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; ON THE RAM TRUCKS STAGE WITH
"DON'T COME LOOKIN'"
JACKSON DEAN!
♪ GOT A HEAD ♪
♪ FULL O' NOISE ♪
♪ 'BOUT A HUNDRED ♪
♪ DIFFERENT THINGS ♪
♪ I'M TRYNA AVOID ♪
♪ I GOT A MIND ♪
♪ IN THE GUTTER ♪
♪ TROUBLE ON ONE HAND ♪
♪ A BEER IN THE OTHER ♪
♪ GOT THE WINDOWS DOWN ♪
♪ AND MY FINGERS CROSSED ♪
♪ JUST LOOKING FOR ♪
♪ A BRAND-NEW WAY ♪
♪ TO GET LOST ♪
♪ SO LONG, FOUR WHEELS TURNIN' ♪
♪ GOT A TANK FULL OF GAS ♪
♪ DOWN THE ROAD I'M BURNIN' ♪
♪ CAN'T SAY I WOULD ♪
♪ AND I CAN'T SAY I WOULDN'T ♪
♪ AND IF I DON'T COME BACK ♪
♪ DON'T COME A LOOKIN' ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; STILL TO HIT THE STAGE,
WE'VE GOT JELLY ROLL,
KELSEA BALLERINI,
AND KANE AND KATELYN BROWN.
PLUS, SHANIA TWAIN PRESENTS
FEMALE VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
BUT UP NEXT, A POWERFUL
PERFORMANCE FROM GWEN STEFANI
AND CARLY PEARCE.
FOLLOW @CMT FOR MORE BEHIND THE
SCENES AT THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS.
TO SUPPORT RELIEF EFFORTS FOR
THOSE AFFECTED BY THE TORNADOES
IN THE SOUTH AND MIDWEST, PLEASE
VISIT www.RedCross.org/CMT.
&gt;&gt; THE 2023 CMT MUSIC AWARDS
SPONSORED BY
RAM TRUCKS, BUILT TO SERVE.
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; WE HAVE A ROOM FULL OF
AMAZING COUNTRY FANS.
BUT I GOTTA KNOW,
WHERE MY GIRLS AT?
WE GOTTA HOLD ON TIGHT
BECAUSE WE ARE ALL ABOUT TO
HAVE A SCREAM SING MOMENT
WITH THIS NEXT SONG.
HERE WITH THE ICONIC
"JUST A GIRL,"
IT'S GWEN STEFANI
AND CARLY PEARCE!
♪ TAKE THIS PINK RIBBON ♪
♪ OFF MY EYES ♪
♪ I'M EXPOSED ♪
♪ IT'S NO BIG SURPRISE ♪
♪ DON'T YOU THINK I KNOW ♪
♪ EXACTLY WHERE I STAND ♪
♪ THIS WORLD IS FORCING ME ♪
♪ TO HOLD YOUR HAND ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ A LITTLE OL' ME ♪
♪ WELL, DON'T LET ME ♪
♪ OUT OF YOUR SIGHT ♪
♪ I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ ALL PRETTY AND PETITE ♪
♪ DON'T LET ME ♪
♪ HAVE ANY RIGHTS ♪
♪ WHOA, I'VE HAD IT UP TO HERE ♪
♪ THE MOMENT ♪
♪ THAT I STEP OUTSIDE ♪
♪ SO MANY REASONS ♪
♪ FOR ME TO RUN AND HIDE ♪
♪ I CAN'T DO THE LITTLE THINGS ♪
♪ I HOLD SO DEAR ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IT'S ALL THOSE ♪
♪ LITTLE THINGS ♪
♪ THAT I FEAR ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ I'D RATHER NOT BE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THEY WON'T LET ME ♪
♪ DRIVE LATE AT NIGHT ♪
♪ OH, I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ GUESS I'M ♪
♪ SOME KIND OF FREAK ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THEY ALL ♪
♪ SIT AND STARE ♪
♪ WITH THEIR EYES ♪
♪ OH, I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ TAKE A GOOD LOOK AT ME ♪
♪ JUST YOUR TYPICAL PROTOTYPE ♪
♪ WHOA ♪
♪ I'VE HAD IT UP TO HERE ♪
♪ ♪
♪ OH! ♪
♪ AM I MAKING MYSELF CLEAR ♪
♪ I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ IN THE WORLD ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THAT'S ALL ♪
♪ THAT YOU'LL LET ME BE! ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ LIVING IN CAPTIVITY ♪
♪ YOUR RULE OF THUMB ♪
♪ MAKES ME WORRY SOME ♪
♪ OH, I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ YEAH, WHAT'S MY DESTINY ♪
♪ WHAT I'VE SUCCUMBED TO ♪
♪ IS MAKING ME NUMB ♪
♪ OH, I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ MY APOLOGIES ♪
♪ WHAT I'VE BECOME
IS SO BURDENSOME ♪
♪ OH, I'M JUST A GIRL ♪
♪ YEAH, LUCKY ME ♪
♪ TWIDDLE-DUM ♪
♪ THERE'S NO COMPARISON ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ I'VE HAD IT UP TO ♪
♪ OH! ♪
♪ WHOA, WHOA,
♪ I'VE HAD IT UP TO ♪
OH, I'VE HAD IT UP TO HERE ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; ONCE AGAIN, SHANIA TWAIN!
&gt;&gt; SINCE THIS NEXT CATEGORY
CHAMPIONS WOMEN IN COUNTRY MUSIC
THAT I DEEPLY RESPECT AND
ADMIRE, IT'S THE PERFECT MOMENT
TO HIGHLIGHT
THE VOICES OF THIS CRAZY
TALENTED FEMALE GROUP,
THE BOYKINZ.
LET'S DO THIS, GIRLS.
SMILES FOR MILES.
WE AIN'T GOT TIME TO WASTE.
JUNK IN THE CITY ♪
♪ WHEN YOU GET STUCK, A LITTLE
LOVE ♪
♪ OWN NAH, NAH, NAH, NAH ♪
♪ GIDDYUP ♪
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU, GIRLS.
NOW HERE ARE THE NOMINEES
FOR FEMALE VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
"WHAT HE DIDN'T DO"
CARLY PEARCE.
"GHOST STORY"
CARRIE UNDERWOOD.
"PICK ME UP"
GABBY BARRETT.
"HEARTFIRST"
KELSEA BALLERINI.
"HEART LIKE A TRUCK"
LAINEY WILSON.
"HUMBLE QUEST"
MAREN MORRIS.
"ACTIN' UP"
MIRANDA LAMBERT.
FEMALE VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
&gt;&gt; AND THE WINNER IS...
LAINEY WILSON.
"HEART LIKE A TRUCK."
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; WHOO!
MY HEART IS ABOUT TO BE TRIED
OUT OF MY CHEST, I'LL BE HONEST
WITH Y'ALL.
THIS SONG IS ABOUT FINDING
FREEDOM AND STRENGTH.
IT'S ABOUT NOT BEING AFRAID OF
THE SCRATCHES AND THE DENTS ON
THE BUMPS ALONG THE WAY WE'VE
ALL GOT A STORY TO TELL AND I'M
SO PROUD OF THIS MUSIC VIDEO.
IT WAS FILMED, PRODUCED, WRITTEN
AND DIRECTED BY ALL WOMEN.
CAN I GET TO "COME ON."
IT IS SO WILD.
I WANT TO SAY FIRST OF ALL,
THANK YOU, JESUS, FOR THIS
OPPORTUNITY.
AND I WANT TO SAY THANK YOU,
CMT, FOR LITERALLY BELIEVING IN
ME BEFORE A LOT OF FOLKS DID.
BUT I ALSO WANT TO SAY THANK YOU
SO MUCH TO THE FANS.
I FEEL LIKE I AM WATCHING MY
DREAMS COME TRUE RIGHT BEFORE MY
EYES, TRULY, Y'ALL.
THIS IS FOR Y'ALL.
I LOVE Y'ALL SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
GOD BLESS Y'ALL.
&gt;&gt; JELLY ROLL IS ABOUT TO TAKE
OVER THE STAGE.
PLUS, ALANIS MORISSETTE
CELEBRATES THE TENTH ANNIVERSARY
OF CMT'S NEXT WOMEN OF COUNTRY
WITH LAINEY WILSON,
INGRID ANDRESS,
MADELINE EDWARDS,
AND MORGAN WADE.
VOTING IS STILL OPEN
FOR THE VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
CAST YOUR VOTES RIGHT NOW ON THE
CMT MUSIC AWARDS FACEBOOK PAGE.
THE VOTING IS PRESENTED BY
RAM TRUCKS.
THE CMT MUSIC
AWARDS CONTINUES.
LIVE FROM AUSTIN, TEXAS.
THIS IS CBS.
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; NICE SHIRT, RIGHT?
MUSIC HAS THE POWER TO UNITE,
HEAL, AND CHANGE LIVES AND
THAT'S WHY WE ARE ALL PROUD TO
SUPPORT ST. JUDE'S CHILDREN'S
RESEARCH HOSPITAL FLIGHT TO END
CHILDHOOD CANCER.
YOU CAN GET YOUR OWN SHIRT BY
VISITING MusicGives.org
ALL PROCEEDS GO TO ST. JUDE
TO ENSURE NO FAMILY EVER
RECEIVES A BILL FROM ST. JUDE
FOR TREATMENT, TRAVEL, HOUSIG
OR FOOD.
THIS NEXT ARTIST CAN BE CALLED
ROCK OR HIP HOP, BUT HIS HEART
IS ALL COUNTRY.
HE'S ALREADY A WINNER TONIGHT.
TEXAS, GIVE SOME LOVE
TO JELLY ROLL!
♪ ♪
HOME
OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ HAIL MARY
♪ I ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
♪ WHEN I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AND I ONLY PRAY ♪
♪ WHEN I AIN'T GOT A PRAYER ♪
♪ SO WHO THE HELL ♪
♪ AM I ♪
♪ WHO THE HELL AM I ♪
♪ TO EXPECT A SAVIOR ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ WHEN I ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
IF I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ BUT, GOD, I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ I KNOW AMAZIN' GRACE ♪
♪ BUT I AIN'T BEEN ♪
♪ LIVIN' THEM WORDS ♪
♪ I SWEAR I SPEND MOST SUNDAYS ♪
♪ DRUNK OFF MY ASS ♪
♪ THAN I HAVE AT CHURCH ♪
♪ HARD COVER KING JAMES ♪
♪ ONLY BEEN SAVIN' DUST ♪
♪ ON THE NIGHTSTAND ♪
♪ AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY ♪
♪ BY THE TIME I FOLD MY HANDS ♪
♪ I ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
♪ WHEN I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AND I ONLY PRAY ♪
♪ WHEN I AIN'T GOT A PRAYER ♪
♪ SO WHO THE HELL AM I ♪
♪ WHO THE HELL AM I ♪
♪ TO EXPECT A SAVIOR ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ IF I ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
♪ WHEN I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AND, GOD, I NEED A FAVOR ♪
YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH, I OWE YOU ♪
♪ MORE THAN ONE ♪
♪ AND BEGGARS CAN'T BE
CHOOSERS ♪
♪ BUT I'LL PAY ♪
♪ FOR ALL I'VE DONE ♪
♪ JUST PLEASE ♪
♪ DON'T LET ME LOSE HER ♪
♪ I ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
♪ WHEN I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AND I ONLY PRAY ♪
♪ WHEN I AIN'T GOT A PRAYER ♪
♪ SO WHO THE HELL AM I ♪
♪ WHO THE HELL AM I ♪
♪ TO EXPECT A SAVIOR ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ IF I ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
♪ WHEN I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AND, GOD, I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ ♪
♪ HANGIN' IN THERE ♪
♪ JUST BARELY ♪
♪ THROWIN' UP PRAYERS ♪
♪ LIKE HAIL MARYS ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE STILL THERE ♪
♪ LORD, SPARE ME ♪
♪ OH, MY GOD ♪
♪ HAIL MARY ♪
♪ HANGIN' IN THERE ♪
♪ JUST BARELY ♪
♪ THROWIN' UP PRAYERS ♪
♪ LIKE HAIL MARYS ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE STILL THERE ♪
♪ LORD, SPARE ME ♪
CMT!
♪ I ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
♪ WHEN I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AND I ONLY PRAY ♪
♪ WHEN I AIN'T GOT A PRAYER ♪
♪ WHO THE HELL AM I ♪
♪ TO EXPECT A SAVIOR ♪
ONLY TALK TO GOD ♪
♪ WHEN I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AND, GOD, I NEED A FAVOR ♪
♪ AMEN ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; FROM THE HIT NETFLIX SERIES
"OUTER BANKS," PLEASE WELCOME
MADISON BAILEY AND CHARLES
ESTEN.
&gt;&gt; JELLY ROLL!
&gt;&gt; MADDIE, EVERYONE KNOWS
THAT WINNING A CMT
MUSIC AWARD IS A HUGE HONOR.
YOU GET RECOGNITION, YOU GET TO
MAKE A COOL SPEECH, AND YOU GET
TO GO HOME WITH A TROPHY THAT
IF I'M HONEST
LOOKS LIKE A PIECE OF TREASURE.
&gt;&gt; IT DOES A LITTLE.
AND IF ANYBODY KNOWS HOW HARD
IT IS TO GET YOUR HANDS ON
TREASURE, IT'S US.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S WHY I'VE HIDDEN THE
TROPHY SOMEWHERE IN THE VENUE,
AND ONLY THE MOST NOBLE AND
RESILIENT HEART WILL FIND IT.
&gt;&gt; WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING TO
JUST GIVE IT TO THEM.
&gt;&gt; FROM CMT GIANTS, VINCE GILL,
WHENEVER YOU COME AROUND.
FROM 2022 CMT MUSIC AWARDS.
CODY JOHNSON.
"NEVER SAY NEVER"
COLE SWINDELL &amp; LAINEY WILSON.
"LET HER CRY"
DARIUS RUCKER
FROM COAL MINER'S DAUGHTER
CELEBRATION OF THE LIFE &amp; MUSIC
OF LORETTA LYNN.
"LAY ME DOWN"
EMMY RUSSELL &amp; LUKAS NELSON.
FROM 2022 CMT MUSIC AWARDS.
"WILD HEARTS"
KEITH URBAN
FROM CMT CROSSROADS:
LEANN RIMES &amp; FRIENDS
"ONE WAY TICKET"
LEANN RIMES WITH ASHLEY MCBRYDE
AND CARLY PEARCE
FROM 2022 CMT MUSIC AWARDS.
"LOVE CAN BUILD A BRIDGE"
THE JUDDS
FROM NAOMI JUDD: A RIVER OF TIME
CELEBRATION.
"THE ROSE"
WYNONNA JUDD &amp; BRANDI CARLILE
CMT PERFORMANCE OF THE YEAR.
&gt;&gt; AND THE WINNER IS...
CODY JOHNSON, "TIL YOU CAN'T."
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ IF YOU'VE GOT A CHANCE,
TAKE IT.
IF YOU'VE GOT A DREAM, SHE
SAID ♪
&gt;&gt; ONCE AGAIN, I DIDN'T PREPARE
ANYTHING TO SAY.
I WILL SAY TONIGHT IT'S GREAT TO
BE IN MY HOME STATE OF TEXAS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
BEFORE I THANK WARNER MUSIC
NASHVILLE, BEFORE I THINK MY
BAND, MY CREW, THIS IS
PERFORMANCE OF THE YEAR.
MY BAND AND MY CREW, THEY HAVE
WORKED TO THEIR TAIL OFF FOR
THIS.
WHAT I PERSONALLY WOULD LIKE
BEFORE I DO THE SAME OLD SPEECH
MOST PEOPLE DO IS WHAT I WOULD
LIKE IS FOR EVERYBODY IN HERE
ALL AT ONCE, ARE YOU HAVING FUN
AT THE CMT AWARDS?
MAKE SOME NOISE.
THAT'S WHAT PERFORMANCE IS ABOUT
AND THAT'S WHAT MY PERFORMANCE
IS ABOUT, YOUR PLEASURE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
GOD BLESS YOU.
THE BLACK CROWES TAKE THE STAGE
WITH DARIUS RUCKER,
HEAD TO YOUTUBE TO GO BACKSTAGE
AT THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS!
WE'RE LIVE NOW.
THIS IS CBS.
&gt;&gt; THE 2023 CMT MUSIC AWARDS
SPONSORED BY LACTAID.
TRY TELLING OUR FARMERS
IT ISN'T REAL MILK.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE WELCOME SUPER BOWL
CHAMPION AND COUNTRY MUSIC
SUPERFAN,
FROM THE KANSAS CITY CHIEFS,
TRAVIS KELCE!
&gt;&gt; CMT, HOW ARE WE FEELING?
IT'S AN HONOR TO BE HERE
TONIGHT.
AFTER SPENDING THE ENTIRE
MORNING IN SOUND CHECK AND THEN
HOURS IN HAIR AND MAKE-UP, IT
TURNS OUT I'M NOT THE KELSEA
EVERYONE WANTED TO SEE PERFORM.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO SEE ME SING
I'LL BE IN THE
PARKING LOT AFTER THE SHOW.
GOING CRAZY ON "WAGON WHEEL,"
A LITTLE BIG GREEN TRACTOR.
I LOVE THIS NEXT ARTIST.
WE RECENTLY GOT TO DO
SNL TOGETHER.
SHE'S BEEN KILLING IT TONIGHT.
MY FRIEND,
KELSEA BALLERINI!
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; YOU FEELING GOOD, Y'ALL?
♪ I'VE KNOWN YOU ♪
♪ SINCE BRAD AND ANGELINA ♪
♪ WE GO BACK LIKE PONTIAC
SEATS ♪
♪ IF I GOT AN AISLE ♪
♪ WITH A MESS I GOTTA CLEAN UP ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU'LL BE ♪
♪ SHOWIN' UP WITH BLEACH ♪
♪ ALL THOSE NAMES ♪
♪ THAT WE DON'T EVER SPEAK OF ♪
♪ GOT A COUPLE NIGHTS ♪
♪ THAT HAVE SLIPPED MY MIND ♪
♪ PROOF AND PHOTOGRAPHS ♪
♪ HAVE BEEN DELETED ♪
♪ IF YOU EVER NEEDED AN ALIBI ♪
♪ 'CAUSE DIRT ON YOU ♪
♪ IS DIRT ON ME ♪
♪ AND WE BOTH KNOW ♪
♪ OUR HANDS AIN'T CLEAN ♪
♪ IF IT ALL BLOWS UP ♪
♪ AND WE END UP ON THE NEWS ♪
♪ IF YOU GO DOWN ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' DOWN TOO ♪
THAT'S RIGHT.
♪ IT'S A GOOD THING ♪
♪ WE'RE EACH OTHER'S ♪
♪ KINDA CRAZY ♪
♪ AIN'T NO JUDGMENT ♪
♪ OR KEEPIN' SCORE ♪
♪ IF YOU ROB A BANK ♪
♪ I'M YOUR GETAWAY MERCEDES ♪
♪ GOD KNOWS THAT'S WHAT ♪
♪ FRIENDS ARE FOR ♪
♪ 'CAUSE DIRT ON YOU ♪
♪ IS DIRT ON ME ♪
♪ AND WE BOTH KNOW ♪
♪ OUR HANDS AIN'T CLEAN ♪
♪ IF IT ALL BLOWS UP ♪
♪ AND WE END UP ON THE NEWS ♪
♪ IF YOU GO DOWN ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' DOWN TOO ♪
YEAH ♪
♪ I KEEP ALL YOUR SECRETS ♪
♪ BY THE DOZEN ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHERE ♪
♪ MY SKELETONS SLEEP ♪
♪ HYPOTHETICALLY ♪
♪ IF YOU EVER KILL YOUR
HUSBAND ♪
♪ HAND ON THE BIBLE ♪
♪ I'D BE LYIN' THROUGH MY
TEETH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE DIRT ON YOU ♪
♪ IS DIRT ON ME ♪
♪ AND WE BOTH KNOW ♪
♪ OUR HANDS AIN'T CLEAN ♪
♪ IF IT ALL BLOWS UP ♪
♪ AND WE END UP ON THE NEWS ♪
♪ IF YOU GO DOWN ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' DOWN TOO ♪
♪ OUR BODIES ARE BURIED ♪
♪ AND THEY'RE IN THE SAME
DITCH ♪
♪ SO EVEN IF I WANTED TO ♪
♪ I CAN'T SNITCH ♪
♪ THIRTY TO LIFE ♪
♪ WOULD GO QUICKER WITH YOU ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ SO, IF YOU GO DOWN ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' DOWN TOO ♪
♪ IF YOU GO DOWN ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; HE'S ONE OF THE HOTTEST STARS
ON CBS'S "FIRE COUNTRY"
PLEASE WELCOME MAX THIERIOT!
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S UP, CMT!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T WANNA BRAG, BUT I GOT
TO WORK ALONGSIDE ONE OF OUR
HOSTS TONIGHT WHEN HE GUEST
STARRED ON "FIRE COUNTRY."
LET ME TELL YOU, HE'S GREAT
IN THE SHOW.
RIGHT NOW WE GET TO SEE HIM DO
WHAT HE ABSOLUTELY DOES BEST.
AND HE'S PERFORMING
WITH HIS WIFE.
HERE WITH THE FASTEST RISING HIT
OF HIS CAREER,
WE'RE GOING BACK OUTSIDE.
IT'S KANE AND KATELYN BROWN!
♪ ♪
♪ I WAS LOST ♪
♪ YOU FOUND A WAY ♪
♪ TO BRING ME BACK ♪
♪ NEEDED FORGIVENESS ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS GAVE ME THAT ♪
♪ GIRL, I'M A WITNESS ♪
♪ OF YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU DON'T BE
GIVIN' UP ♪
♪ AND IT'S CRAZY ♪
♪ HOW YOU SAVED ME ♪
♪ HAND ON THE BIBLE ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW HOW I GOT YOU ♪
♪ BUT I COULDN'T ASK FOR MORE ♪
♪ GIRL, WHAT WE GOT'S ♪
♪ WORTH THANKING GOD FOR ♪
♪ SO THANK GOD ♪
♪ I GET TO WAKE UP ♪
♪ BY YOUR SIDE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOUR HAND FITS ♪
♪ PERFECTLY IN MINE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOU LOVED ME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO ♪
♪ BUT YOU DID ♪
♪ AND YOU DO ♪
♪ AND HE KNEW ♪
♪ THANK GOD FOR GIVING ME YOU ♪
♪ THANK GOD ♪
♪ THANK GOD
♪ NEVER THOUGHT I'D FIND ♪
♪ AN ANGEL UNDERCOVER ♪
♪ MADE A CHANGE TO EVERYTHING ♪
♪ FROM MY HEART ♪
♪ TO MY LAST NAME ♪
♪ HEY ♪
♪ HARD TO TELL, WHEN HE FELL ♪
♪ THAT BOY WAS HEAVEN SENT ♪
♪ AND EVERY NIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ BEFORE I SAY AMEN ♪
♪ I THANK GOD ♪
♪ I GET TO WAKE UP
BY YOUR SIDE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOUR HAND ♪
♪ FITS PERFECTLY IN MINE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOU LOVED ME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO ♪
♪ BUT YOU DID ♪
♪ AND YOU DO ♪
♪ AND HE KNEW ♪
♪ THANK GOD FOR GIVING ME YOU ♪
♪ THANK GOD ♪
♪ HAND ON THE BIBLE ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW HOW I GOT YOU ♪
♪ I COULDN'T ASK FOR MORE ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ GIRL, WHAT WE GOT'S ♪
♪ WORTH THANKING GOD FOR ♪
&gt;&gt; ♪ SO THANK GOD ♪
♪ I GET TO WAKE UP
BY YOUR SIDE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOUR HAND ♪
♪ FITS PERFECTLY IN MINE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOU LOVED ME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO ♪
♪ BUT YOU DID ♪
♪ AND YOU DO ♪
♪ AND HE KNEW ♪
♪ THANK GOD FOR GIVING ME YOU ♪
♪ I THANK GOD ♪
♪ I GET TO WAKE UP
BY YOUR SIDE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOUR HAND ♪
♪ FITS PERFECTLY IN MINE ♪
♪ AND THANK GOD ♪
♪ YOU LOVED ME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO ♪
♪ BUT YOU DID ♪
♪ AND YOU DO ♪
♪ AND HE KNEW ♪
♪ THANK GOD FOR GIVING ME YOU ♪
&gt;&gt; CMT, MAKE SOME NOISE FOR MY
BEAUTIFUL WIFE ONE TIME.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU!
&gt;&gt; FROM THE RAM TRUCKS STAGE,
WITH A DEBUT PERFORMANCE OF HER
SONG "NARCISSIST,"
HERE IS ANNA AVERY.
♪ MY PARENTS DON'T LIKE YOU ♪
♪ WHY WOULD THEY WANT TO ♪
♪ AFTER THEY FOUND ME ♪
♪ CRYING ON THE BATHROOM FLOOR ♪
♪ I DON'T EVEN LIKE ME ANYMORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU SAY ♪
♪ THAT I'M CRAZY ♪
♪ YOU SAY THAT YOU'RE SORRY ♪
♪ WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN ♪
♪ YOU SAY I'M DRAMATIC ♪
♪ I'M OVERREACTING ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I AM ♪
♪ AND I KNOW ♪
♪ YOU GET OVER ME ♪
♪ BUT CAN YOU GET OVER
YOURSELF ♪
♪ BEFORE YOU ♪
♪ GO AND LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD PROBABLY ♪
♪ GET SOME HELP ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; NEXT, THE BLACK CROWES
AND DARIUS RUCKER.
PLUS, PERFORMANCES FROM
ALANIS MORRISETTE
AND CARRIE UNDERWOOD.
TIME IS RUNNING OUT TO CAST
YOUR VOTE FOR VIDEO OF THE YEAR,
PRESENTED BY RAM TRUCKS.
GO TO THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS
FACEBOOK PAGE AND COMMENT RIGHT
NOW TO VOTE AND FIND OUT WHO
WINS IN JUST A BIT.
THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS CONTINUES.
LIVE FROM AUSTIN, TEXAS.
THIS IS CBS.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE WELCOME THE ARTIST
WITH THE MOST CMT MUSIC AWARD
WINS EVER.
AND SHE'S UP FOR
ANOTHER ONE LATER TONIGHT.
CARRIE UNDERWOOD.
&gt;&gt; EARLIER THIS WEEK DARIUS
RUCKER TOOK THE STAGE HERE IN
AUSTIN WITH THE BLACK CROWS FOR
AN UPCOMING EPISODE OF "CMT
CROSSROADS THIS MAY.
NOW THEY ARE PERFORMING ONE OF
MY FAVORITES "SHE TALKS TO
ANGELS."
IT'S THE BLACK CROWES
AND DARIUS RUCKER!!
♪ SHE NEVER MENTIONS ♪
♪ THE WORD ADDICTION ♪
♪ IN CERTAIN COMPANY ♪
♪ YES, SHE TELLS YOU ♪
♪ SHE'S AN ORPHAN ♪
♪ AFTER YOU MEET HER FAMILY ♪
♪ SHE PAINTS HER EYES ♪
♪ AS BLACK AS NIGHT NOW ♪
♪ SHE PULLS THOSE SHADES ♪
♪ DOWN TIGHT ♪
MY GIRL, GIVE A SMILE ♪
♪ WHEN THE PAIN COMES ♪
♪ THE PAIN THE ONLY THING ♪
♪ TO MAKE IT ALL RIGHT
♪ SAYS SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ THEY CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ OH, YEAH, YOU KNOW
SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ THEY CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ SHE KEEPS A LOCK OF HAIR ♪
♪ IN HER POCKET ♪
♪ SHE WEARS A CROSS ♪
♪ AROUND HER NECK ♪
♪ YES, THE HAIR ♪
♪ IS FROM A LITTLE BOY ♪
♪ THE CROSS IS SOMEONE ♪
♪ SHE HAS NOT MET ♪
♪ NOT YET ♪
♪ YEAH SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ THEY CALL HER OUT
BY HER NAME ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ SAYS THEY CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ SHE DON'T KNOW NO LOVER ♪
♪ NONE THAT I EVER SEEN ♪
♪ BUT TO HER ♪
♪ THAT DON'T MEAN NOTHIN' ♪
♪ BUT TO ME ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW ♪
♪ MEANS EVERYTHING ♪
♪ SHE PAINTS HER EYES ♪
♪ AS BLACK AS NIGHT, NOW ♪
♪ SHE PULLS THOSE SHADES
DOWN TIGHT ♪
OH, YEAH ♪
MY GIRL, SHE WANTS TO
GIVE A SMILE ♪
♪ WHEN THE PAIN COMES ♪
♪ THE PAIN THE ONLY THING ♪
♪ TO MAKE IT ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ THEY CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ THEY CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ THEY CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ YES THEY DID ♪
♪ SHE TALKS TO ANGELS ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW
THEY CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ CALL HER OUT ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW ♪
♪ BY HER NAME ♪
♪ CALL HER OUT ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; SHE'S ONE OF THE MOST
POWERFUL VOICES IN COUNTRY.
PLEASE WELCOME LEANN RIMES.
&gt;&gt; HELLO, EVERYONE!
WHAT AN INCREDIBLE PERFORMANCE.
THAT WAS A DREAM COME TRUE.
WE ARE GOING TO SHOW THE MEN OF
COUNTRIES AND LOVE.
THESE GUYS HAVE TURNED OUT TRULY
UNFORGETTABLE SONGS AND VIDEOS
THIS YEAR SO SOME MUCH-NEEDED
RECOGNITION IS IN ORDER.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR BEST
MALE VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
"ROCK AND A HARD PLACE"
BAILEY ZIMMERMAN.
"HUMAN"
CODY JOHNSON.
"SHE HAD ME AT HEADS CAROLINA"
COLE SWINDELL
"SON OF A SINNER"
JELLY ROLL
"LIKE I LOVE COUNTRY MUSIC"
KANE BROWN.
"THE KIND OF LOVE WE MAKE"
LUKE COMBS.
"WASTED ON YOU"
MORGAN WALLEN.
MALE VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
&gt;&gt; AND THE WINNER IS...
JELLY ROLL!
"SON OF A SINNER."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; I LOVE Y'ALL SO MUCH.
THANK YOU, CMT, BABY!
THREE AWARDS IN ONE NIGHT!
I HOPE Y'ALL GIVE ME A SECOND
HERE.
I'M A LITTLE EMOTIONAL.
I STARTED DRINKING.
I DIDN'T THINK I WAS GOING TO
WIN AGAIN.
IT MAY HAVE LOOKED LIKE IT WAS
ONLY 30 YARDS, BUT IT TOOK ME 39
YEARS TO WALK FROM OVER THERE TO
WRITE HERE.
IN I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I
DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH BUT I KNOW
YOU CAN OVERCOME IT.
I PROMISE YOU YOU CAN.
AND YOU CAN BE WHATEVER YOU WANT
TO BE.
I PROMISE YOU THAT.
I TOLD THEM I WANTED TO BE A
COUNTRY MUSIC SINGER AND I'VE
SEEN HERE AT THE CMT AWARDS WITH
THE MALE VIDEO OF THE YEAR, BA
BABY!
WHEN GOD HAS GOT SOMETHING FOR
YOU, NOTHING CAN GET IN YOUR
WAY.
MAMA, I KNOW YOU'RE WATCHING.
MAMA, LOOK AT YOUR BABY BOY.
I'M FIXING TO GET DRUNK DOWN
DOWNTOWN.
I WANT TO THANK COUNTRY RADIO
FOR ACCEPTING ME KNOWING WHO I
WAS LETTING ME DO IT MY WAY THE
WHOLE WAY TO THE STAGE TONIGHT.
THAT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME,
Y'ALL.
I WANT TO THANK THE COUNTRY
MUSIC COMMUNITY FOR STANDING
BEHIND ME AND STANDING NEXT TO
ME THROUGH ALL THIS AND FOR
EVERYBODY IN THIS CROWD, LISTEN
CLOSE.
THIS WILL BE THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING I SAY TONIGHT.
WE ARE SHUTTING SIXTH STREET
DOWN TONIGHT, BABY!
&gt;&gt; COMING UP,
AN EPIC PERFORMANCE
FROM ALANIS MORISSETTE
WITH COUNTRY'S RISING STARS
LAINEY WILSON, INGRID ANDRESS,
MADELINE EDWARDS,
AND MORGAN WADE, PLUS
CARRIE UNDERWOOD LIGHTS UP
DOWNTOWN AUSTIN.
THE ALL-STARS OF COUNTRY AND
ROCK CELEBRATE THE LEGENDRY
LYNYRD SKYNYRD.
FOLLOW @CMT EVERYWHERE FOR MORE
BEHIND THE SCENES AT THE
CMT MUSIC AWARDS!
&gt;&gt; THE 2023 CMT MUSIC AWARDS
SPONSORED BY
PROGRESSIVE.
SAVE WHEN YOU BUNDLE
AUTO, HOME, OR MOTORCYCLE
INSURANCE.
&gt;&gt; PLEASE WELCOME BACK
CARLY PEARCE!
&gt;&gt; 10 YEARS AGO, CMT LAUNCHED
ITS NEXT WOMEN OF COUNTRY
PROGRAM, A MEANINGFUL AND
THIS GROUNDBREAKING
INITIATIVE HIGHLIGHTS
A NEW CLASS OF RISING WOMEN
AND PROVIDES THEM WITH
CAREER-CHANGING OPPORTUNITIES.
SINCE THEN, OVER 100 ARTISTS,
INCLUDING MYSELF, HAVE BEEN
SUPPORTED THROUGH THE PROGRAM,
OPENING DOORS AND MAKING CLEAR
THAT OUR VOICES ARE VITAL TO
COUNTRY MUSIC.
TONIGHT, FOUR OF THEM ARE HERE
TO PERFORM WITH A WOMAN WHOSE
MUSIC BECAME THE DEFINING
SOUNDTRACK FOR GENERATION X.
HER ALBUM "JAGGED LITTLE PILL"
IS ONE OF THE BEST-SELLING
ALBUMS OF ALL TIME AND THE SONG
"YOU OUGHTA KNOW" BECAME AN
ANTHEM FOR WOMEN.
WITH THE PERFORMANCE HONORING
THE 10-YEAR ANNIVERSARY OF NEXT
WOMEN OF COUNTRY,
PLEASE WELCOME LAINEY WILSON,
INGRID ANDRESS,
MADELINE EDWARDS, AND MORGAN
WADE, WITH THE ONE AND ONLY
ALANIS MORRISSETTE!
♪ I WANT YOU TO KNOW ♪
♪ THAT I'M HAPPY FOR YOU ♪
♪ I WISH NOTHING BUT ♪
♪ THE BEST FOR YOU BOTH ♪
♪ AN OLDER VERSION OF ME ♪
♪ IS SHE PERVERTED LIKE ME? ♪
♪ WOULD SHE ♪
ON YOU IN A THEATER ♪
♪ DOES SHE SPEAK ELOQUENTLY? ♪
♪ AND WOULD SHE HAVE YOUR
BABY? ♪
♪ I'M SURE SHE'D MAKE ♪
♪ A REALLY EXCELLENT MOTHER ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE LOVE ♪
♪ THAT YOU GAVE ♪
♪ THAT WE MADE ♪
♪ WASN'T ABLE TO MAKE IT
ENOUGH ♪
♪ FOR YOU TO BE OPEN WIDE ♪
♪ NO ♪
♪ AND EVERY TIME YOU ♪
♪ SPEAK HER NAME ♪
♪ DOES SHE KNOW
HOW YOU TOLD ME ♪
♪ YOU'D HOLD ME UNTIL YOU DIED ♪
♪ TILL YOU DIED ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL ALIVE ♪
♪ AND I'M HERE ♪
♪ TO REMIND YOU ♪
♪ OF THE MESS YOU LEFT ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WENT AWAY ♪
♪ IT'S NOT FAIR ♪
♪ TO DENY ME ♪
♪ OF THE CROSS I BEAR ♪
♪ THAT YOU GAVE TO ME ♪
♪ YOU, YOU, YOU ♪
♪ OUGHTA KNOW ♪
♪ YOU SEEM VERY WELL ♪
♪ THINGS LOOK PEACEFUL ♪
♪ I'M NOT QUITE AS WELL ♪
♪ I THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW ♪
♪ DID YOU FORGET ABOUT ME ♪
♪ MR. DUPLICITY ♪
♪ I HATE TO BUG YOU ♪
♪ IN THE MIDDLE OF DINNER ♪
♪ IT WAS A SLAP IN THE FACE ♪
♪ HOW QUICKLY I WAS REPLACED ♪
♪ AND ARE YOU THINKING OF ME ♪
♪ WHEN YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE LOVE ♪
♪ THAT YOU GAVE ♪
♪ THAT WE MADE ♪
♪ WASN'T ABLE TO MAKE IT
ENOUGH ♪
♪ FOR YOU TO BE OPEN WIDE ♪
♪ NO ♪
♪ AND EVERY TIME ♪
♪ YOU SPEAK HER NAME ♪
♪ DOES SHE KNOW
HOW YOU TOLD ME ♪
♪ YOU'D HOLD ME UNTIL YOU DIED ♪
♪ 'TIL YOU DIED ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL ALIVE ♪
♪ AND I'M HERE ♪
♪ TO REMIND YOU ♪
♪ OF THE MESS YOU LEFT ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WENT AWAY ♪
♪ IT'S NOT FAIR ♪
♪ TO DENY ME ♪
♪ OF THE CROSS I BEAR ♪
♪ THAT YOU GAVE TO ME ♪
♪ YOU, YOU, YOU ♪
♪ OUGHTA KNOW ♪
♪ ♪
♪ AH, AH, AH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THE JOKE ♪
♪ THAT YOU MADE ♪
♪ IN THE BED THAT WAS ME ♪
♪ AND I'M NOT GONNA FADE ♪
♪ AS SOON AS YOU
CLOSE YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND YOU KNOW IT ♪
♪ AND EVERY TIME I SCRATCH ♪
♪ MY NAILS ♪
♪ DOWN SOMEONE ELSE'S BACK ♪
♪ I HOPE YOU FEEL IT ♪
♪ WELL, CAN YOU FEEL IT? ♪
♪ YEAH, I'M HERE ♪
♪ TO REMIND YOU ♪
♪ OF THE MESS YOU LEFT ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WENT AWAY ♪
♪ IT'S NOT FAIR ♪
♪ TO DENY ME ♪
♪ OF THE CROSS I BEAR ♪
♪ THAT YOU GAVE TO ME ♪
♪ YOU, YOU, YOU ♪
♪ OUGHTA KNOW WHY I'M HERE ♪
♪ TO REMIND YOU ♪
♪ OF THE MESS YOU LEFT ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WENT AWAY ♪
♪ IT'S NOT FAIR, TO DENY ME ♪
♪ OF THE CROSS I BEAR ♪
♪ THAT YOU GAVE TO ME ♪
♪ YOU, YOU, YOU ♪
♪ OUGHTA KNOW ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; WITH THE SONG THAT WON HER
CMT MUSIC AWARDS NIGHT,
"TENNESSEE ORANGE," HERE TONIGHT
ON THE RAM TRUCKS STAGE,
IT'S MEGAN MORONEY!
♪ TOOK ME TO KNOXVILLE ♪
♪ LAST SATURDAY ♪
♪ AND I WORE THE HAT ♪
♪ ON HIS DASH TO THE GAME ♪
♪ IT SURE WASN'T ATHENS BUT I ♪
♪ FELL FOR HIM ♪
♪ UNDER THOSE NEYLAND LIGHTS ♪
♪ I MET SOMEBODY ♪
♪ AND HE'S GOT BLUE EYES ♪
♪ HE OPENS THE DOOR AND HE ♪
♪ DON'T MAKE ME CRY
♪ HE AIN'T ♪
♪ FROM WHERE WE'RE FROM BUT HE ♪
♪ FEELS LIKE HOME, YEAH ♪
♪ HE'S GOT ME DOIN' THINGS ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER DONE ♪
♪ IN GEORGIA ♪
♪ THEY'D CALL IT A SIN ♪
♪ I'M WEARIN' TENNESSEE ORANGE ♪
♪ FOR HIM ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; VOTING FOR VIDEO OF THE YEAR
HAS OFFICIALLY CLOSED.
FIND OUT THE WINNER LATER.
BUT NEXT, CARRIE UNDERWOOD TAKES
OVER DOWNTOWN AUSTIN ON OUR
CAPITOL STAGE.
AND LATER, AN ALL-STAR TRIBUTE
OF GARY ROSSINGTON
AND LYNYRD SKYNYRD.
WE'RE LIVE BEHIND THE SCENES OF
THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS!
CHECK IT OUT ON YOUTUBE NOW.
THIS IS CBS.
&gt;&gt; STILL HANGING OUT BACK HERE
IN THE SOLITAIRE GRAND HARVEST
GAME LOUNGE.
CODY ALAN IS GETTING HIS CHANCE.
LETS KEEP IT GOING WITH SINGER
AND SOCIAL MEDIA SENSATION,
WHOSE NEW SINGLE IS OUT FRIDAY.
DIXIE D'AMELIO!
LET'S GO!
&gt;&gt; THIS PERFORMER IS AN
INSPIRATION TO ANYONE WHO
HAS EVER TAKEN THE STAGE,
AND YOU ARE ABOUT TO SEE WHY.
SHE BRINGS IT WITH EVERY NOTE
EVERY TIME, WHETHER SHE'S
PERFORMING ON HER SOLD OUT TOUR,
HER HIT LAS VEGAS RESIDENCY,
OR RIGHT HERE ON CMT.
TEXAS, MAKE SOME NOISE
FOR MY FAVORITE,
CARRIE UNDERWOOD!
♪ ♪
♪ I'M FREE AS A BIRD ♪
♪ NO TIES ♪
♪ NOTHIN' KEEPING MY WINGS ♪
♪ FROM FLYING HIGH ♪
♪ AND GOING OUT ON THE TOWN ♪
♪ ON A SATURDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HE'S GONE ♪
♪ WITH THE WIND ♪
♪ AND LORD KNOWS I DESERVE ♪
♪ TO BE FLIRTED WITH ♪
♪ BUT THE ONLY PROBLEM IS ♪
♪ I HATE MY HEART RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ UNDERNEATH THE COVERS ♪
♪ IN THE DARK RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ WISHIN' I WAS ♪
♪ SITTING IN A BAR RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ TWO DRINKS IN ♪
♪ MAKIN' ME A LAST CALL FRIEND ♪
♪ I WANT MY FEEL GOOD BACK ♪
♪ INSTEAD OF FEELING BAD ♪
♪ THAT I CAN'T GET PAST ♪
♪ THE FACT THAT I CAN'T LOVE
NOBODY ELSE ♪
♪ I WOULD IF I COULD ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW ♪
♪ I HATE MY HEART ♪
♪ RIGHT NOW, YEAH ♪
♪ HATE MY ♪
♪ HEART RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT HIM BACK ♪
♪ THAT AIN'T IT ♪
♪ BUT THIS THING IN MY CHEST ♪
♪ JUST CAN'T FORGET ♪
♪ IT KEEPS BEATING FOR HIM ♪
♪ AND IT JUST WON'T QUIT ♪
♪ I HATE MY HEART RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ UNDERNEATH THE COVERS ♪
♪ IN THE DARK RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ WISHIN' I WAS SITTING ♪
♪ IN A BAR RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ TWO DRINKS IN ♪
♪ MAKIN' ME A LAST CALL FRIEND ♪
♪ I WANT MY FEEL-GOOD BACK ♪
♪ INSTEAD OF FEELING BAD ♪
♪ THAT I CAN'T GET PAST ♪
♪ THE FACT THAT I CAN'T LOVE
NOBODY ELSE ♪
♪ I WOULD IF I COULD ♪
♪ BUT I DON' KNOW HOW ♪
♪ I HATE MY ♪
♪ HEART RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ I HATE MY HEART RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ ONE DAY I PRAY ♪
♪ HE'LL STAY OUT OF MY HEAD ♪
♪ I KEEP WAITING ♪
♪ BUT IT AIN'T HAPPENED YET ♪
♪ I HATE MY HEART RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ UNDERNEATH THE COVERS ♪
♪ IN THE DARK RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ WISHIN' I WAS ♪
♪ SITTING IN A BAR RIGHT ♪
♪ NOW ♪
♪ WITH A TALL, DARK LAST CALL
FRIEND AND MY ♪
♪ FEEL GOOD BACK ♪
♪ INSTEAD OF FEELING BAD ♪
♪ THAT I CAN'T GET PAST ♪
♪ THE FACT THAT I CAN'T LOVE
NOBODY ELSE ♪
♪ I WOULD IF I COULD ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW ♪
♪ I HATE MY HEART RIGHT NOW ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD BE DOING
SOME SQUATS AFTER THAT BUT IT'S
OKAY.
AND NOW FOR THE FINAL
PERFORMANCE
ON THE RAM TRUCKS STAGE, WE'VE
GOT A BAND WHO DOLLY PARTON
SAYS HAS A FUN NEW TAKE ON ONE
OF HER SONGS.
PERFORMING, "YOU CAN HAVE HIM
JOLENE," THIS IS CHAPEL HART.
♪ OH, JOLENE ♪
♪ YOU CAN HAVE HIM ♪
♪ 'CAUSE HE DON'T ♪
♪ MEAN MUCH TO ME ♪
♪ WELL, I'VE CRIED SO MUCH ♪
♪ TIL RIVERS TURNED TO SEAS ♪
♪ OH, JOLENE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU THINK ♪
♪ THAT HE'S IN LOVE ♪
♪ HE'LL SURELY LEAVE ♪
♪ LIKE HE DID ME ♪
♪ YOU CAN HAVE HIM, JOLENE ♪
♪ YOU CAN HAVE HIM ♪
♪ JOLENE ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; COMING UP,
DARIUS RUCKER HANDS OUT
THE BIGGEST AWARD OF THE NIGHT,
VIDEO OF THE YEAR,
AND THEN WE'RE CLOSING THINGS
OUT WITH AN UNFORGETTABLE
STAR-STUDDED CELEBRATION OF
SOUTHERN ROCK GIANTS
LYNYRD SKYNYRD.
THE CMT MUSIC AWARDS CONTINUES.
LIVE FROM AUSTIN, TEXAS.
THIS IS CBS.
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE BEEN VOTING ALL
NIGHT LONG TO HELP PICK THE
WINNER OF OUR BIGGEST AWARD, NOW
IT'S TIME TO FIND OUT WHO IS
GOING HOME WITH IT.
ARE YOU GUYS READY TO KNOW WHO
IS GOING TO WIN?
THESE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR VIDEO
OF THE YEAR.
&gt;&gt; "HATE MY HEART"
CARRIE UNDERWOOD
"WAIT IN THE TRUCK"
HARDY FEATURING LAINEY WILSON
"THANK GOD"
KANE BROWN AND KATELYN BROWN
VIDEO OF THE YEAR.
&gt;&gt; AND THE WINNER IS...
KANE BROWN AND KATELYN BROWN
"THANK GOD."
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; OH, MY GOSH.
OH, MY GOSH.
FIRST OFF, I AM SO NERVOUS.
THIS IS SO NEW TO ME.
WHEN WE RECORDED THE SONG A YEAR
AGO, I NEVER IN MY LIFE WOULD
EVER THINK THAT THIS WAS EVER
GOING TO HAPPEN.
BUT I JUST WANT TO SAY THANK YOU
SO MUCH TO MY AMAZING HUSBAND.
I LOVE YOU.
THIS IS A SPECIAL THAT WE GET TO
SHARE THIS TOGETHER EVERY NIGHT
AND I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
&gt;&gt; I'LL BE QUICK.
I WANT TO SAY THANK YOU TO THE
FANS THAT VOTED.
THANK YOU TO SONY, MY AWESOME
MANAGER, THIS IS ALEX.
HE MOVED HERE FROM BARCELONA.
HE WANTED TO BE A VIDEO
DIRECTOR.
HE HAS DONE ALL OF MY MUSIC
VIDEOS.
HE IS MAKING THE AMERICAN DREAM
COME TRUE.
I LOVE YOU!
THANK YOU, CMT!
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU!
&gt;&gt; PLEASE WELCOME
A GRAMMY WINNING ICON,
PETER FRAMPTON!
&gt;&gt; I AM HERE TONIGHT
TO HONOR NA FRIEND AND TOURMATE
OF MINE
GARY ROSSINGTON WAS A SOUTHERN
ROCK ICON.
HE WAS AN ORIGINAL FOUNDING
MEMBER OF THE BELOVED GROUP
LYNYRD SKYNYRD, ALONGSIDE
RONNIE VAN ZANT
AND ALAN COLLINS.
GARY NOT ONLY HELPED DEFINE THE
BAND'S SOUND, HE INSPIRED
MILLIONS OF FANS AND MUSICIANS.
HE HAS NOW JOINED HIS FELLOW
SKYNYRD BAND MATES IN ROCK
AND ROLL HEAVEN BUT WE WILL ALL
ENJOY THEIR MUSIC FOREVER.
GARY'S WIFE AND BANDMATE DALE
AND DAUGHTER MARY,
RICKEY MEDLOCKE,
AND JOHNNY VAN ZANT ARE
HERE TONIGHT
AS WELL AS RONNY'S
WIDOW, JUDY VAN ZANT,
AND HIS GRANDDAUGHTER, ARAYAH.
THANK YOU ALL FOR SHARING THIS
MOMENT WITH US.
IT'S MY PLEASURE TO
WELCOME
MEMBERS OF ZZ TOP, BAD COMPANY,
GUNS N' ROSES, THE ALLMAN
BROTHERS.
I AM RUNNING OUT OF FINGERS.
THREE OF COUNTRY'S GREATEST
VOICES, LED BY THE
ROLLING STONES' MUSICAL DIRECTOR
ON KEYS.
THEY ARE ALL HERE TO PAY TRIBUTE
TO GARY AND THE KINGS OF
SOUTHERN ROCK!
LYNYRD SKYNYRD!
HERE ARE CODY JOHNSON,
BILLY GIBBONS,
PAUL RODGERS, SLASH,
CHUCK LEAVELL, WARREN HAYNES,
AND OUR HONKETTES FOR TONIGHT
WYNONNA JUDD AND LEANN RIMES!
♪ ♪
&gt;&gt; YEAH, YEAH
♪ MY MAMA TOLD ME ♪
♪ WHEN I WAS YOUNG ♪
♪ COME SIT BESIDE ME ♪
♪ MY ONLY SON ♪
♪ AND LISTEN CLOSELY ♪
♪ OH, BABY ♪
♪ TO WHAT I SAY ♪
♪ AND IF YOU DO THIS ♪
♪ IT'LL HELP YOU ♪
♪ SOME SUNNY DAY ♪
♪ AH, YEAH ♪
OOH, OOH ♪
♪ GARY WAS A SIMPLE MAN ♪
YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ OH, TAKE YOUR TIME ♪
♪ DON'T LIVE TOO FAST ♪
♪ TROUBLES WILL COME ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ AND THEY WILL PASS ♪
♪ YOU'LL FIND A WOMAN ♪
♪ YEAH, YOU'LL FIND LOVE ♪
♪ AND DON'T FORGET, SON ♪
♪ THERE IS SOMEONE UP ABOVE ♪
♪ AND BE A SIMPLE ♪
♪ KIND OF MAN ♪
♪ OH, BE SOMETHING ♪
♪ YOU LOVE AND UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ BABY BE A SIMPLE ♪
♪ KIND OF MAN ♪
WON'T YOU DO THAT
ANYTIME YOU CAN ♪
♪ BABY, BE A SIMPLE ♪
♪ KIND OF MAN ♪
♪ OH, BE SOMETHING ♪
♪ YOU LOVE AND UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ BABY, BE A SIMPLE ♪
♪ KIND OF MAN ♪
♪ OH, WON'T YOU DO THIS ♪
♪ FOR ME, SON ♪
♪ IF YOU CAN ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
TURN IT UP NOW!
♪ BIG WHEELS ♪
♪ KEEP ON TURNIN' ♪
♪ CARRY ME HOME ♪
♪ TO SEE MY KIN ♪
♪ SINGIN' SONGS ♪
♪ ABOUT THE SOUTHLAND ♪
♪ I MISS ALABAMA ONCE AGAIN ♪
♪ AND I THINK IT'S A SIN, YES ♪
♪ ♪
♪ WELL, I HEARD MISTER YOUNG ♪
♪ SING ABOUT HER ♪
♪ WELL, I HEARD OL' NEIL ♪
♪ PUT HER DOWN ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ WELL, I HOPE ♪
♪ THEY WILL REMEMBER ♪
♪ A SOUTHERN MAN ♪
♪ DON'T NEED HIM AROUND ANYHOW ♪
♪ SWEET HOME ALABAMA ♪
♪ WHERE THE SKIES ARE SO BLUE ♪
♪ LORD,
♪ SWEET HOME ALABAMA ♪
I'M COMIN' HOME TO YOU ♪
♪ ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ ALABAMA ♪
♪ ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ ALABAMA ♪
♪ ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ YEAH! ♪
&gt;&gt; OH, MY GOSH, DID YOU GUYS
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HAVE FUN TONIGHT?
SO LOADED WAY.
AS ALWAYS.
THANK YOU TO THE BEST FANS IN
THE WORLD.
&gt;&gt; CONGRATULATIONS TO ALL THE
WINNERS.
AND THANK YOU, TEXAS!
GOOD NIGHT!
♪ ♪
♪ SWEET HOME ALABAMA
♪ SWEET HOME ALABAMA ♪
♪ ♪
♪ H, YEAH! ♪
♪ SWEET HOME ALABAMA ♪